Don't you see rubies dripping from my hair like rice?
Size!
They name her, you chished of the half-eating grace
Chandelini barefoot on the threshold of place
Where jasmine borders wilt into wilderness
And purity unlearns its own loneliness
Not in the lotus-white halls where mantras are in
Green stone, skipped across the lake of the socialino
won't be saved. Hey everybody, how are you? I'm not just making it from the
waist down. Are you sleeping? Tired? Or is it sleep?
So relaxed. Hi Jamie. So relaxed. Are you so relaxed?
What are you doing?
Well, I hope we see her I hope she comes and it was it was a crazy night last night. It was a crazy
Oh, you're just relaxed.
You're just so relaxed.
She's like totally,
she's like totally just like,
what do you want a massage?
Do you want a massage?
Oh, hi.
You're coming over, thank you.
Came over to say hi.
Where's Tux?
Tux was here last night and Tux was good.
He like, Lola went into the little room
and sort of meowing.
He went in there and said hi to her.
Hi.
How's everyone doing?
Okay. Add a little dinner, nice coffee. I have like, I hardly drank any of my drink last night, so
how the rest of it should be. It's not too bad. That's why I like the kind of freer drinks,
because I kind of get, I'm a little bit, oh, what are you saying? What? Hey, you're talking to me?
Hi, you're talking? That's what he's like, he's like meow, he's like meow, he's like meow, okay.
Maybe I'll have some more food. Maybe I'll have salad tonight, that's not that good.
Did you like the picture? That was made by Alexandra, she took, you know, bae clips, you know,
the one that was like, you know, I looked like, you know, golem, and she made him look nice, so.
appreciate it. Also she also did a really nice review of the Codex today and
played a couple of my videos and a pretty awesome show and so thank you
Alexandra. That was really cool, thank you. And how's everyone doing? Yeah I had an
end last night because Q, well you know what he did, he started saying the end
word a bunch of times like over and over. I mean that's really like not
Cool to do like why would he do that? I don't understand
All they can do is hurt like it can't help anything. It can only hurt
So that's I kind of like an aggressive aggressive move
Interesting things. I'm gonna keep for your band for that. I
Don't know. I don't think so
Now I just encourage everyone else to do that. So
Maybe I will
We need to get maybe you could get a dick pic maybe then maybe I'll forgive them
Hi, Lenore.
Come on, there you go.
Oh, yeah.
I think I have bird legs.
Birdie.
So, well, it's quiet.
I do have a little presentation tonight.
It's a short little slideshow that I made.
And it's actually done a lot of slideshows
about the toxic personalities and narcissists
and psychopaths and stuff that I've never done.
Um, I've never covered the subject which I'm going to cover which is pretty interesting
and it's more like my personality, but it's
It's called something different, but also you'll see you'll see I'm just gonna wait for some more people to get in here
How are we doing so it's like I mean it's like I don't know people who just come in here to like lurk or if they like
Or afraid of Kate or whatever. Don't be afraid of her. She's just a big bully
I mean she
It's so funny. It's like because I've been really like looking into these group dynamics of like
How these like groups and how they hey, what's up, Audrey? How are you? These groups are their hierarchies, right?
And it's like and so then it's like and then nobody's really allowed to question them or it's like or it's like basically
They're out of there. So the only thing you can do is like say I don't care if I'm out of the group
Kate and making that face. Yeah, exactly. I don't care. I mean say I never felt like I was part of the group anyway
I don't understand this with some whole like community part of it where it's like and
Now Kate is like, you know, she was talking to beat again, and like they're getting along now. Isn't it? It's so weird
But then be to even they have the recognition number like okay, well if we're gonna get along it's just because we hate
Hey, it's like he's so much. I am free. Yeah. F the group, right? And it's like, and then they're
like, Oh, well, we're not going to go over there anymore. It's like, do I care?
About these people that don't want to come here is that obviously there weren't that good of like, you know
Supporters or friends in the first place if they're just can like, you know fucking write me off and want to
Bad for me and we'll tell everyone and but I just don't like that
No, there are a lot of people that are like maybe like afraid and I don't want I don't like the idea of people being silenced or anything
Hi, Audrey
so
You know, but I've kind of I've never been part of a group or anything, you know
I'm gonna say that's why I'm not joint. I don't join like, you know organizations really and like I don't like oaths
Except like ones I make to myself. I like to I don't like
you know, I
I'm not into groups per se
and I'm more of like the the lone wolf to Sigma energy, right?
and
That's kind of almost what the presentation tonight. It's gonna be about a little bit these Sigma types
Which are like, you know, I walk alone
Yep, so but how is everyone's day? So is they able to say Tuesday Tuesday Tuesday is the day of Mars?
So what is it? It's almost Wednesday though. It's always a oh, yeah, it's almost Wednesday Wednesday. I was yeah, they're bullies
I mean they really are and
And also a beat of said she said
Oh my god, Psyche is like, you know, talking about his, he's, he was traumatized and he was bullied.
She's like, this is not the place to talk about those things. Why are you talking about that kind of, like, hey, bitch.
Let me, first of all, I can talk about whatever I want. Second of all, it's like, well, especially things like that.
You don't pick sides, you slip half a day, so it's, well, sometimes it's, sometimes you, sometimes there are sides to pick.
I mean, it's like, but yeah, you don't have to like, you know, say it, but I mean, it's like.
Lot of people have been taking sides and
Yeah, I don't she really doesn't I mean she she doesn't there's like and I don't know she has
I mean it. She'll be like, oh he's talking. I mean literally
She had a six hour live. I get hey, what's up Sharon? How are you good to see ya? Oh my god
I'm just like up the count although my bare legs. There was a norm. Just a kind of just give you a little massage
Good to see you Sharon
Sharon Watson
Yeah, and then like, you know, there's a little there's a few other things going on right now, but I
Just I think that
There's like in groups they like there's like targets sometimes and I've been a target and I've been a slander and
Bullied and all this kind of stuff. And so in you know, and so
I mean, it's not like everybody's anybody's perfect, right?
All sweet all she does is all sweet peed is she's obsessed Audrey isn't she and she's like and they're like
Oh my god
He's getting Sharon I was thinking Sharon noodles too because Sharon noodles. I was one this is a drag queen with
Um, she's singer. I shanine. Yeah, I was thinking that just now for some reason
But um, yeah, they're Sharon noodles as a drag queen and she has a song called 666. It's really good
I like and I wish I could play more more music on the show than I do, but
It's pretty cool. Yeah, Jamie's here
The whole gang is back together.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, the band but trumpet, oh my God.
She's in the band called but trumpet?
Oh my God, that's not a very nice name.
My God, Lenore's just running around.
Yeah, Jamie's here.
Oh my gosh, my necklace came off.
I'm a little my medallion necklace. I have it. I mean already the
Thing broke a little bit so it has to put
the
Class to put the class one. It's just right right thing. You can do it and then put it on around my neck
I think it will still fit
There's another share needles another one
Are you talking about sharing needles? No, you should never do that. Nobody should ever do that
I'm just kidding. Sharon Osborn.
Vita has a grudge against Jamie's Cowboys.
I know, but, you know, secretly, you know, it's like,
she likes people that don't, that hate me, right?
And so, you know, I think, and so, and so,
and if she was to like, you know,
if Jamie and I have ever had a fight or something,
I think she would kind of try to swoop in and say,
oh, come to my show.
And like have Jamie if they're just like to like say I'm a terrible person or something
I don't know. I know Jamie would never do that. The Norse were panther. Yeah, I know Jamie's very loyal
And she would never do that, but I would have put it past
you know
The praying mantis woman to try that
Yeah, yeah, Jamie had a little break
Everybody because she's she's been she's been here
Almost, no, she's been here since the beginning,
and so, there it goes, okay, I gotta fix this.
There we go, and I can put that through there.
How do women do this with these little tiny claps?
You have to be like on a microscope, okay, there it goes.
And it goes like that.
This is my medallion of the sun, okay.
Oh my God, just popped up, oh my God, break it.
I just had it.
I mean, essentially when those women, hey, when women,
hey, money, how are you?
When women have such like, like long nails,
how do they do this?
Is this what the husband has to do?
They're like, oh, how do you can you put this on me?
On me?
I don't know.
They must have be like little like ninjas
with their fingernails, huh?
I don't know.
I'll have to put it on later.
And I like, I'll just wear my one medallion.
I'll take it out today.
It's an interesting one.
little patterns on it. I have my nails are clean tonight so I can show the stuff over there you go.
And this is the back of it. It's pretty. I like, I do like, I do believe in like the power of
I think it's just future, but I got my rings.
I think one of my rings is like possessed by a spirit
or something, I used to be into,
there's like a little spirit keeping
and I don't know if it's just like a,
I mean, it's like, but they're an etsy,
they used to sell these rings that were like possessed.
Yeah, oh, yeah, and I have this,
and then I have this,
Bracelet, I hate when these bracelets break though
They're throwing these little like elastic things and eventually they like will fall off and they'll all fall over the floor
I have a beautiful piece that has a beautiful purple stone right there. I like that
Yeah
Yeah, and I
Have a lot of cool things actually about it. I'm gonna see if you use the I'm gonna start take I'm gonna take about and share them
Pretty soon. I mean, but I thank you so much
Yeah, but I like my big rings and
Um, Alexandra was saying today like she's like she said she liked my style and I'm kind of
like
Like a like a drug lord a little bit like a drug my dad
So she's mentioned like my buttons or sometimes undone my dad used to like
Where the we're sure similar to this or he was yours. He wore these shirts called Tommy Bahama
He really loved these Tommy Bahama shirts. He was even my dad was a good dresser
He always had a hat. He had these felt hats
Glasses and he was a pretty good dresser and all with you know suits and stuff
but
But he would wear these these kind of
Tommy Bahama shirts and it's like they start up with like a few buttons that and then when he sometimes at dinner
They'd like throughout the dinner the trucker. He got they go. He got more and more buttons would be open
But um, yeah, my dad was really funny. He was a you know, he's a businessman, but like they take business call and
To people would be like what's what's that noise? I hear I heard way of bubbles or
It's what's that sound he'd be in the jacuzzi taking business calls. He just loves that in the pool jacuzzi and stuff
Maybe yeah, he's very very relaxed and
Yeah, he was he never used a computer. Hi Marcy. How are you sweetie?
Yeah, I need to remod some people. I know and I do apologize
I know I've like modded and I know some because you know, I just I'm always unmodding everybody and then like starting over and stuff
So I'm happy to see like who but um, it's like
usually I
Don't
Usually it's not like it's I just do everybody or something like that, but I get you
And if anyone like
Because right now it's right now. Hey, oh my gosh easy. Are you okay? I was worried about easy a little bit. I
Was worried. Are you okay easy? I'm glad you're here. I
Woke up today. The first thing I did was turn on the turn on like easy easy
Oh, he's on. I went on
He was like yelling and I don't know if he wants to share too much but I was like oh my gosh
hope you're okay. Okay now this is not working. I guess this is frozen. Okay are you okay?
Yeah my dad's buttons he'd be like halfway down. I'll just hang on with my father.
Also, he had these shirts and I had this pillow
and it's like my family friend made these shirts
and it's like, here's a shirt I used to wear.
I mean, they turned it into a pillow, a pillowcase.
Shan, are you like, but it's like the people
that are here right now, I do really appreciate
because I've been like, you know, there are people saying,
oh, don't go to the show unless you press them
or and don't support him, just unsubscribe from him.
Like just, but like, I don't think really a lot
of people did or are doing it.
Like I see a lot of people still coming and stuff,
I don't like
Who are these people that think they're like the queen of the queen of the YouTube or something like that?
Like to tell people what to do and who to subscribe to or where to go. I don't understand. I mean, yeah
And it's like and also it wasn't like it was like basically people were making demands that I do things and it's like
I'm not just like not I didn't just fall not fall in man's but it's like I didn't
Know the person that I mean very well, and so I was like I did and so all these things and
But it's like a lot of people will be pressured. We've been put under pressure to like that. I was like
I'm just because I would appreciate if somebody looked into it, if I was being slandered,
I would like, because people would like, I see all the time people on beat is like,
oh my god, I would never go to his chat. I would only go there because of you. And it's like,
you know, I never go there anymore, because he's just disgusting. And, you know, he's dirty and
you know, abuses his cats. I mean, it's all those narratives. And it's like the people that just
Meeting me. I mean, it's like if you're if you if you come here, you know, like my cats love me and like here we go
Trace is trying to use to the month. I'm so sorry. It's like it's freezing. There we go. Yeah
um
And then kind of dry doxing too because it's like, you know, she's putting her
her stream name is like some as like with my last name up there
But it's like the last name of a celebrity and so
So she put the celebrity up there and says it looks like the Victoria girl
But I think she's just putting up to annoy me because I do see she has goons
She has the goon squad and now look at for Barry
He is in this I'm packed pack it up or something and he's her head goon. I saw the picture of it. Okay. Here. I got finally got it
He actually like contacted me and he's like I can't cover your your chat anymore because because Kate would
Um, Kate said, Kate said, I can't and I was like, what?
I was like, I think for real.
I was like, well, I was like, well, he's like, I'm afraid of her.
And I was like, well, I said, don't be afraid of her.
I love Shrek and then.
And then all of a sudden, she made a meme of like Shrek.
I was like, well, it wasn't Shrek,
but it was like some beautiful AI Shrek princess
with almost like, and with her picture that she used.
And then she made me the donkey, which was kind of funny.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, go wherever you want.
Like wherever you, I mean, go to hers.
I mean, I was promoting her up until this point
and clumsy being gang and stuff.
And it's like, and you know,
Well, maybe not like some people like I mean
like not
Like you know RG has always been like I was like I kind of had a side-eye on RG
And it's like a lot of people like you know like him and he's like nice and cordial
But I think he's like maybe part of like now
I'm noticing more of these group dynamics where I didn't notice these connections before but now I'm seeing like I
See the board. I see like which where everyone is on the board and stuff like that and I'm like I feel like I'm kind of like like a
Maybe not even playing like me. I sometimes don't feel like a player, but it's like most of this and I'm just watching
I like to all right, but as oh here we go. Okay, so I'm gonna get back to my streamer. So wait, so I got that
Yeah
Okay
So I do have a little presentation though if you want to see and this will be a cool presentation
And so let me just get my notes for this. Okay
You have some notes. I wonder if I can
Okay, well
I'm gonna have to put it up like this and just do half screen. Okay
After the video, I told you to look at.
Oh, you go over after the, after, yeah, easy.
I mean, that's the, okay.
So I'm actually, I made a new, I made a new song.
So I'll play the song first.
This is a new song I made today.
And this is based on, it's kind of like,
I almost did one based on that video you showed me,
but this is like, it was like,
I did it kind of like on the same topic though.
And it's basically, you'll see.
It's actually, I think you'll like it.
It's about groups and stuff like that and enjoy this.
Yeah?
You won't even, you won't even ban once.
Here we go, watch this.
Here you go.
I'll be right back.
Don't speak yet.
Watch who everyone looks at first.
Got a rhythm here, every laugh is engineered
Eyes flick up before they speak
Permission dressed as just be me
And timing tight reactions trained
Nothing random in this game
Every thought already weighed
Before it ever leaves your brain
You feel it shift, but no one names it
Truth walks and gets rearranged quick
built for true watch the leader subtle cues micro smirks decide your views one
cold pause can shut it down one wrong step you're out the crowd they all
Twist
You learn comfort, I learn fight
Strings in the ceiling, cutting loose
Nothing left for me to lose if it breaks
When truth is said, it was already hanging dead
They don't silence you
They make you silence yourself
Hit your frame, I won't play your quiet game
Boundaries clean, no disguise, no more filtered eyes
What do you wanna see, Barry?
Is that Barry?
Wait, what do you wanna see?
The buddy troll song?
Are you the buddy troll, Barry?
I think Barry's pack yourself up.
You are, I did like your art that you did though.
I do have to say I liked your art.
I didn't like the art that was me.
I don't know if you made that, but that was, I mean,
I mean, I'd say that was fine, I mean, I don't know.
I really, I've seen, I've been,
it's fine if people call me some sort of,
I'm a, I find, I've actually kind of like,
you're not Barry, are you Samman?
Because I'm back. I mean, I don't know. I don't know. It's a mystery. Thank you, Marcy. You're like that
I mean, thank you so much. Yeah, I'm trying to put a lot of education in the songs because it's like and Alice was
Totally right. Alexander. She was like, I think that or she's like
I'm gonna play some of these like in the car and stuff because she's like it kind of is like there's lessons in them and stuff and so
I have one called the art of power.
It's really, I'll play it later.
But I do want to do a short little presentation.
And so let me bring it up.
It's, so this will be good, I promise.
Okay, bring up the slide, okay.
Okay, well, here's, okay, so let me see slides.
And computer, okay, upload.
And here it is, okay.
So here we go.
Okay, this will be good it's not I you know I've done a lot about a lot of
different personality types but you're not gonna heard this personality type
okay this one's called the ones nobody warned you about right okay
the ones nobody warns you about.
And let me pull up my prepared notes.
So.
So so whatever to share isn't comfortable and it's not meant to be so we spend a lot of time talking about the people who hurt
Us loudly, but nobody ever warns you about the quiet ones the ones who've already been through the fire
So this presentation is about them
Okay, the ones nobody warns you about
Okay
So
So, they didn't read a book about healing, they didn't watch a seminar, they were in
it for years sometimes, decades of chaos, betrayal, dysfunction, and they came out on
the other side with something most people will never develop, an absolute clarity about
who they are and what they'll accept.
Right?
Okay.
Sorry if it's hard to see, I need to, okay.
It's a little small.
So trauma creates hyper observance
as a survival mechanism.
So when someone's mood can turn dangerous in seconds,
you learn to read micro expressions,
tone shifts and energy changes.
And so the presentation about these people,
these people still carry that skill.
They see what you don't say.
They notice the gap between
your words and your behavior.
And they stay quiet about it,
not because they're forgiving it,
but because they genuinely don't care enough to fix you.
Okay.
And so we expect disruption to be loud,
a confrontation, an accusation,
but trauma-borne loners don't need any of that.
They disrupt by simply being present, by not nodding along, by refusing to co-sign with
other people's version of reality.
Their silence is the earthquake, their stillness is the mirror.
And what unsettles people isn't cruelty, it's the clarity.
It is a skill, but it's also it's it's developed because of you know trauma, you know
Which I was told not to talk about my trauma
But I think it is actually helpful to like talk about because I think a lot of people have experienced it
Especially nowadays so this is about the one that really breaks people. So
So some walk-in is a fixer the helper or the wise one and offer advice and position themselves and
These people just don't respond the way people usually do.
They don't lean in.
They say thanks and move on because they've already survived their worst day without you.
So their self-sufficiency is destabilizing and it's meant to make people ask, who am
I without being needed?
Here's the uncomfortable truth underneath the helper identity when
When someone needs people to need them. It's not really about them. It's about control. It's about
Staying at the center of attention. So trauma-borne loners see this pattern instantly
They've had people help them with invisible strings attached their whole lives. So when they decline the help, they're not being cold
They're just refusing the transaction. That's why everyone was saying. Oh, we're just trying to help you. We're just trying to help you
And I was like, well, I don't need help because I know what I know what I'm doing. You're back, right? Okay, so
And so then we get into
These buying games so they don't work on these people so it's hot and cold push and pull paths of aggression
Silent treatment these tactics only work on people who are desperate for connection people who fear abandonment and up to chase to beg
To apologize for things they didn't do
Trauma-borne loners have already been abandoned. They've already survived the worst case. So when
So when people go silent hoping that they'll chase them they don't and the non-reaction is the most disorienting thing
Some people have ever experienced
Okay, and it's the boundaries are not bluffs
Most people say they respect boundaries. What they mean is I respect boundaries that don't inconvenience me
So trauma-borne loners have non-negotiable limits because they know what life feels like without them
They don't yell when you cross the line. They don't argue. They just leave quietly and permanently and in that clean quiet exit
Some sense of entitlement gets exposed often
Okay
So these people do not shrink
So pay attention to how much you're reassured
when some people collapse,
when someone over explains or apologizes too much
or makes themselves smaller to fit other people's comfort.
That signals to people, I'm controllable.
So trauma-borne loners stopped doing that a long time ago.
They're not shrinking,
they're not feeling silence to ease others discomfort
and that refusal, the simple refusal to make themselves
small is deeply unsettling to people who need
Other other people to diminish in order for themselves to feel large, right?
So
Confidence doesn't need an audience, but performance does.
So watch the difference.
A performer walks in scanning the room for reactions,
adjusting their energy,
and managing their impressions that they make.
But the self-possessed person just walks in
and speaks without over-justifying.
They get misunderstood and they stay okay with it.
Their internal stability is built on a lived truth,
not external feedback.
And so when
there's someone who relies on external consensus to feel real standing next to that kind of
groundedness is almost unbearable, right?
So there's a difference between someone who's
a read about running a marathon and someone who's actually run one.
And you can hear it.
One quotes principles and the other describes
a specific day, a specific pain,
a specific decision they've made
when everything in them just wanted to stop.
Trauma-borne loners speak the second language.
And while some people are still living in theory
when they talk about growth, but they haven't done the work,
the gap becomes plainly visible.
Okay.
And so there are
No natural reaction to trauma-borne loners people either feel drawn to them curious inspired or wanting to understand
what that kind of self-knowledge looks like or
They feel defensive irritated suddenly certain the person is cold or arrogant or broken
The second group they're not reacting to the loner. They're reacting to the mirror
They're seeing something in themselves that they've been working very hard not to look at
Okay, because alignment is disruptive
In a world where most people are fragmented, say one thing, doing another, presenting polished
surfaces while hiding a mess underneath, someone who's whole will stand out.
Not because they're trying to, but alignment and people that are aligned simply are, while
some actions match values every day, including when it costs something, that coherence disrupts
every room they walk into, not a performance as a fact of being.
And so we're wrapping it up.
And so at first it's a relief when they go
because they're too intense, it's too much.
But a few days pass and the question surfaces
were quiet and relentless.
Why was it so easy for them to let me go?
And the answer, when you're finally honest enough
to see with it, they didn't leave
because people are worthless.
If they left because they know their own worth
and they weren't going to compromise not for anyone.
Okay, and so in conclusion
So we made it here. Okay, we made it to the end of this presentation. It's a very short little presentation. Okay. I hope you enjoyed
Something in this
Shifted something in you, but I can tell because you're still here listening. So here's the choice you have you can click away go back to
comfortable patterns
and let this presentation just fade away
like a notification or you can sip, but the discomfort.
Ask yourself questions that make you uncomfortable
because that discomfort, that's the shake
and the shake is where the growth begins, you know?
And that's that, that's my presentation on that.
Uh-oh.
Was I, did you hear me?
Was I gone?
Did you hear me at all?
Oh my God.
Did you hear me? Oh my god, how embarrassing. Well, at least I hope you read it. I
Helped you with it. Okay. Okay. I hope you like the presentation
I'm gonna okay, I'm good. Okay. Thank God. Okay. Thank God. Oh, yeah. Okay. Well I am
You know
I have had that, you smoke too weed, you're not good at multitasking,
just listening to two different panels.
You heard? Okay, good, good, good.
Well, because I had a very traumatic time with these people in Glendale,
and I had this trap house in Glendale,
I'll tell personal stories now.
Your cousin pulled up a smoke and blunt, and that's nice.
Yeah. So.
you know, I got, I was stabbed actually. And, uh, and so when they talk about these learning,
these micro expressions and like learning to read the room and the energy and things like that,
and also just being gay. Like I've been, I've been, I went to this party when I was probably like
17 or 18, this girl took me to a party. And, um, I think it was like, I think it was like a bunch
of Nazis. You relate to several scenarios and different points. Oh, you're welcome. I mean,
Like I'm like enjoying making these now because I like making the songs too, but I
Want to do I do want to like share more more like these personal things like
So it's just basically survival. It's um
But also I just know how it feels to be excluded. Okay, but it's sort of this party. Yeah, yeah
I just I just felt like something very I was like, let's get out of here
It was I think it was a way
I think there were a bunch of Nazis actually and I and then they started like chasing like chasing us
Oh, and I had to jump in the car and stuff like that. And so who rolled in who rolled in like a tumbleweed. I
But yeah, so it's like some of these things like, you know
I have to be more sensitive to my environment, especially because there's like there are more dangers
Especially for people like me that are like, you know hit on straight people
I'm lucky. I've never gotten like, you know, but um
Yeah, and then I have been stabbed and stuff and oh big pipes
Where's mr. Oh my god, mr. Big pipes terrified door dorks. I'm not terrified
Are you terrified mr. Rude mr. Rude pipes?
Where have you been?
Look who rolled in like a tumbleweed, right? Oh my god. I must be protected. Thank you. Thank you. I'm a you know, I
um, I
Just don't feel like people want to really throw me away because I I mean even like I was listening to beat is and they had
Like the NorCal and everyone's just talking shit
But at the same time he did say something was interesting. He's like he's like well
Because Sam was like, oh my god. Well, he's like that I saw you over that last night and they're guys like
Well, I see you over there all the time too and they're like they're like well
we're kind of addicted because you know
Like he likes to see the crash out or whatever Sam. I like the drama and stuff um and
And so it's like and I really don't care like people were laughing at me or with me. I like to entertain
I'm an entertainer. I'll play the clown sometimes
I like to entertain, and so some people get the joke,
some people don't, some people,
I also say things with a straight face a lot.
Like, I have kind of a dry sense of humor sometimes,
and so I'll say things totally serious,
and it's like, people are like, what?
And I'm like, well, I'm just cating in it, but I'll,
you know, I think it's a Capricorn thing.
Capricorns usually have a pretty dry, wicked sense of humor.
Okay, let me.
Sam and secretly has a crush on me. You can't stay away. I know and it's like all the better. It's like I wish
It's like, you know, I wish people had a crush on me. We would just like say it and be nice
if you're a mod and
If you if you mod him and not you you're opening both bands. Oh my god. Okay. Hold on
Oh my goodness me. Yeah. Oh, I know I'm not I'm not ever gonna make him a mod
I mean, I can't believe he's still allowed in the chat that is like I don't know he like
I'm such a sucker sometimes for like even like because he'll come up and talk in a soothing way and then it's like it's kind of like
Okay, dude, the thing is I just don't like being told what to do and I don't like being pressured by like the group about things
You know, but like I said, I can be impressionable like the like I said recently the right guy
He could probably talk me into robbing a bank like and you know
So I can't really like date because it's like too dangerous because I'd be too easily manipulatable by the wrong person and I have
You know an empath do you tend to tend to attract?
Psychopaths narcissists like or other they say sometimes and but or you know and other empaths too
But also, some people see them as suckers or stuff like that, and it's like, maybe I can be kind of a sucker.
I'm not like a dick sucker. All these people are like, oh my gosh, he just wants to suck all these guys' dicks, and then it's like, maybe some of the guys I do.
But really, I think my hitting on people is more of a shtick, you know?
It is more of a...
It's like, you know, most of the time I don't even see them, but they but these guys they take it so personally and they're like, oh my god
He's sexually harassing us and oh how dare you it's like
And especially like white like like what why I don't understand like why?
It's like are they're not a protected
Well, I mean I'm more to be protected but some of these some of these some people are like not necessarily like a protected like
protected class of people because it's like
Um, you know, like, and there, and plenty of these guys are very comfortable to her as people too.
It's like, that's why I kind of started doing it.
Like I had this woman, Piranha, and she would like, I'd have her like tell the guy to take off his shirt and stuff, and she would like to do it.
To get kind of like revenge for like the time she gets hit on but she doesn't want to be hit on
I know like I know women understand the harassment like women women are totally sexually harassed like a lot
And that it's become almost you know, unfortunately almost almost like just a normal thing
But you know, so no, what is it wrong? What is it wrong to get it back?
I mean, yeah, I'm a little I'm a little bit of a I'm a little bit of a troll that way, right?
So here you go, Shane. There you go
Okay, here you go
I'm sorry my computer's freezing a little bit. I don't know. I think I have, hey Ms. Liz, I think I have
too much on my computer and stuff. So, but anyway, um, so it was just really funny what
happens, like, and then, then I was like, well, I'm sure you're going to come around and do what
the group wants and stuff. And then I was told, I was part of, I was like, this is what the, well,
Kate said, the community got together and decided something and everyone agreed.
And I was like, I've never heard of that. What community?
But I don't know how to play you Eugeo, and I think I mean I wasn't even good at card games when I was like a kid
I
Think he just basically I don't know if he plays it or he just like goes and collects them or something
But I saw Kate did play a video of him like buying all these
boxes of
Eugeo cards and you know, it's like whatever and I
Collected stickers when I was like eight years old or something or seven years old
I don't know. It's like people collected beanie babies and stuff. I mean a clutch collecting is fine
I guess there is maybe money in it, but I don't know if he like I think some people like way too long
Because they will eventually like like beanie babies the market the bubbles is burst
Like a little good look at like remember them beanie babies like a thousand dollars for like a little unicorn beanie baby
And then it's like now they're like, you know
There's giving them a dollar or two dollars. So and
A lot of people just bake the beans, you know, inside of them, you know, and how they really
dried beans, I'm not sure.
But remember those stupid beanie babies, and they have the...
I don't they're just it was crazy remember Pogs. Yeah, we so when I was little we had the we had first
We had these like we had Pogs, which were like these like a little thing
You'd like throw like a little yeah, whatever this called like us because these are one of those coins
I could dummy coin or something like that a slug
We call them slugs and you throw the slug down and it would flip and stuff like that and they'd go into
I don't know. I was not good at like doing that
But yeah, they had Pogs and then I had these little the Japanese store. They had a Japanese supermarket
And they would sell this like cookies and the cookies are to be the little holographic sticker of like and I would have just Japanese on it and then be like really great and I was just there just be like so unusual and
And I would love collecting those little stickers and also they can some trading cards and stuff but my little brother
With like always getting my stuff and like I had the slammer. Yeah, there's you have a slammer thing
You got a big you got me you're charging your headphones right now. Okay, you're gonna come up. Cool
I want to talk to mr. Big pipes. We'll see what kind of gangster plays you Geo
I don't know but it's like yeah, I don't think he's a really a gangster like I mean he's just like I
Don't know what he I mean. It's like he's an unusual character
Q made a good point where it's like I was like well everyone's everyone I said everyone seems to like like him because I
Made kind of a mean joke. You should you should hit a page that are no district types is about to chill. Oh
Let me let me let me call her right now
Page will probably be here the page does come quite often and so but
I think she's not into it.
I don't think she wants to be dating right now.
So yeah, but yeah.
Hey, I just want to chill.
Remember that, Mr. Big Pipes?
I just want to chill.
And you said, and you used to say, don't be so jelly.
You're in the bed pan disciples?
Ooh.
Oh my God.
I said that's a sweet pee of mine,
but it says sweet pan of mine.
I like that.
Salutes.
Hello, pink.
Sweet pan.
Pipes needs a hetero barrier on the panel.
And, uh, I'm right. And yeah, I mean, it's like, just like the way they're talking, she's like, I don't think I'll let psyche on my panel and we're like, Oh, no, because what, I can't come on your panel and I like five people gang up on me and, you know, say terrible things and, and, you know, but, um, and there, and, and then it's like, there's a lot of hypocrisy in the community too, because there's, there's such a similar.
There's always these exceptions and they'll be attached to somebody that's also controversial.
I'm not really going to call anybody out because I don't believe in like excluding people based.
Like I said, unless people sometimes like in jail or they've done something like really,
and even if they've done something really terrible, I'm happy. I'd like to talk to them still.
And even the North cow is like, oh, he thinks he's Howard Stern. Oh, that Howard Stern in your head.
He didn't have any controversial paths.
Howard Stern used to do skits in a clan outfit
and say the N-word and stuff like that on this show.
And so yes, and also like,
and he was very controversial, so I don't understand.
They don't but they can't give me they can't give me any props. They can't give me any like, oh, I'm like
I'm just like apparently I'm all I'm good for is like crashing out or whatever. I'm not a good interviewer
I don't try to understand anybody. I don't I don't like I mean, it's like it's just like they don't get it done
And so yeah, Daniel Carver and you know the funniest Daniel Carver thing was is that Daniel Carver like they did a
They sent a film crew to his house. I think during Howard TV and they interviewed his wife
and his wife would say the n-word and stuff, but she collected black dolls.
You heard Sweepie had a breathing attack from going upstairs? Oh my god.
Well, sweetie is like, oh, I'm sure he's received money a hundred percent sure because of court like I receive my like like no
It's like and that wouldn't I mean I remember but first and first I'm like
I'm horrible to my donors and then I'm just protecting my donors, right?
It's like it's like everything I do or like our accused of doing it's criticized no matter what it is on both sides, right?
She did well, I hope she's okay if she did. I don't I don't want to mean but you're like actually like
you know, be any pain or, you know, I wish, I do wish the best for people, but it's like,
they don't wish the best for me really. They're like, yeah, or, you know, they're like basically
like, oh, just freeze them out of the community or not the community. Like I'm in a community, but
like, all of a sudden, Kate's and Beat are getting along. And, but they do have enough
self-awareness is like, well, we're kind of just, we're kind of just hate bonding because we both
hate psyche right now. And so
That's not the healthiest kind of foundation for our for a friendship, right?
Because those just send a term so it's better to subond over like, you know
Common interest besides who you hate, you know, but some people do like they missed it
So yeah, Daniel Carver is one of the first Howard Stern. So this is you saw your older brother's friend. Yeah
Yeah, okay, so I had those tapes to the channel nine tapes
I bought them on eBay these video cassette tapes and it was from channel nine show, which was like opposite Saturday at live
It was like on another channel channel nine in New York. I don't think it was around the country really
It was just like in New York. I think but it would out do it out
Perform Saturday at live. It was such a good show, right?
And then there was really funny episodes where they had he had like easy eon
I mean there, but he had a bunch of celebrities and Richard Simmons were the classic ones
No link today. Yeah, there's a link. I'm gonna put the link. I'm so sorry
I'll clean it too. I'm just my computer is a little bit slow because I
Got all this stuff on it. Okay
This is who a cop
Yeah, today no car was real clansmen and he had a hit a line and it said wake up white people
I hope you're doing well too, Liz.
I don't wanna look at, let me see.
See, and it is, my YouTube keeps freezing.
It's like, I'm having trouble doing the mod thing.
The second you ever play, yeah, hold on.
See, that's been frozen.
To use a cop, oh, well, you ever see
Oh Brother Where Art Thou?
And it's like, yeah, in that kind of movie,
like all the cops are in that.
Do you not join YouTube?
Why not?
Arthur, what are you saying?
Like when to meet yeah to watch out for those
Well, the thing about clans people is like there's actually black people in the clan too because you can't really see
My god, you can't really see you through the rope. You can't really see and so there are there's like a black a black guy that infiltrated the clan
Miss Liz. Why are you saying do not join YouTube are there? Why are you saying that? What does that mean?
You mean I'm not joined my show or do not
Cause yeah, people have been warned by, you know, Kate, do not go to his show, do not
be in his chat unless you're going to press him about this and this, like really.
And uh, and there's such, I mean, some of these things like Tommy, Tommy James is like
being this moral, this moral crusader to me and he's actually like, just like three days
ago he was doing meth and fentanyl for $10 a hit.
I heard everyone criticized me for putting up.
Song request for five dollars, but no one said anything to tell me James, right? His name is pipes taxi. Yeah
Yeah, oh you're talking to pipes. Yeah, you're not joining
Just join mr. Bigfoot. Well, yeah, Mr. Bigpipes used to join and then he'd start we'd be talking and then all of a sudden
We hear like the banjo start playing in him singing well over us. Oh, of course I would I would date any race
I would but I have I haven't I've only dated like one person. Yo, what's up?
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
You already know.
Hey, what's up?
How are you doing?
What happened today?
Do you want to talk about it or no?
It don't matter to me.
It was intense.
It was fast, it was intense.
Yeah, cuz I went over to Stephen King's this afternoon
I was like, does anyone have an update on easy and then he said, oh psyche
We're not talking about that. Just don't bring it up because you know, I don't want to talk
Did you or did you not? No, okay. Thank God. So so this I saw this on your page
I don't want help you don't mind if I share this image, but I don't care guys show show whatever you want to show
I don't like you psyche. I'm not gonna try you ever. I'll put it away. I put most of my stuff away
So I don't know what you want to show. Oh, oh, yeah, huh? That's great. Yeah
Yeah, and yeah, he said so he had this on his post and I was like well
I hope it was I hope it was a good day for easy and I hope you didn't get that
I said a good day cuz you know, um
The old me. Yeah, the old me would never did what I did today
Okay, and what was that? Tell us a little bit about it. If you don't mind I'd like to the old me with his ass
Okay, that's today. I come down and you know
You run into this person or and we live in the same complex is
Inevitable, you know, it's like I want to go get I want to go go to store some beers and food and
When I walk out the store, I see an old friend. I'm talking to I see my other friend
He pulls up we talking and then next they know this guy just walked past and I'm like that's him
Look that's him. So no one that this man docs me and did this and look at my family and all that crazy shit
You know all that stalking shit. Yeah
So I I approached him. Yo, what's up? Why you did all that?
Well, before I when the mini this man locked eyes on me his soul left his body
He's like, you know how you see that skin face like you saw a ghost
Yeah, yeah, that's what happened in and then he instantly pulled out his phone
I was walking tip to press axum. Yo, why you dox me? I did this way did that he's like anyone one, please help
Well, maybe he's bluffing, but I mean it's like I hopefully you don't have a warrant. No, no
It was it's all record. There was a video. There's a short if you want to play the short play the short
I'll let you play it on your it's on your own page. Yeah, it's on page. You can play the short. I give you permission
Okay, I'm not gonna strike you for shit and nothing
Oh, I know you
It's like he this guy right here that he talks a lot of shit about you. Oh, he does. I don't even know this person
I'm gonna go by Matthew NYC. Oh, I might have it might have been on a panel with or
Yeah, there's multiple panels of him talking a lot of shit about you. This is the guy. This is how he looks
This is what happens when you talk shit and dox people online and you get questioned in real life about it
This is what happens. He goes to 911
Yeah, I mean, oh, yeah, here we go. So I found your face. Oh my gosh. I see him. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh
Your first reaction was oh my gosh
You see the way he's talking his lip and it's funny
Here you go guys, this is I guess his name is mathy. Okay. I thought he said I thought I was a math mathy
But here we go math. Yeah. Yeah. So that's him. Okay
And let's have a look at this clip so he's pulling out the phone
Yeah, this is after I walked up to him like we're at I walked up to him he easily pulled out the phone
Fuck out of me bro. Look at him calling 9-1-1. Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. I'm recording bitch ass nigga
You're a bitch ass nigga talking all that
Oh my god, look at his face
With you see the teeth with these teeth
Fuck you gonna do nigga. The fuck you don't drunk right the fuck you gonna do and I was so
Attack me you gonna hit me
My hands is not in my pocket nigga, bitch ass nigga, my hands is not in my pocket, you bitch ass nigga, I'm not touching you, you a bitch ass nigga, call 911 nigga, you little bitch, don't touch me, don't touch me, you little bitch, don't touch me, I'm asking you not to touch me, why you touch me?
Nobody next to you nigga, I'm on camera right now, not on one, I'm on camera right now, nobody's touching you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Okay, that was it. Wow. Okay. Wow. Oh big pipes. Wow. Been a minute. You've been big pipes. You're back
Wow, look at you. You're upgraded. You look like you have a nice back. You got a plan on now. Holy shit
Wow
Hold on
That's my
My audio and shit working. I can hear you but a little low
What's the average is on average but I can hear you if anybody starts really yelling
then nobody doesn't sound better like if I tell you go right there so I just got there's
Great, well, how are you? I'm chillin, dude. Are you are you are you I'm high on a wheat?
Yeah, I'm kind of drunk too. I just like I haven't I haven't really drank alcohol in like a couple months
So yeah, I remember when you used to drink like a whole bottle of something
I got I've been drinking one a day one a day one beer or what women won't yes
Okay
What's on your what is your shirt say Vans if you were in Vans shirt? Are you wearing a wig or is that your real hair?
That's my real hair dude. Okay. Can you pull it? Can you pull it? Yeah, I guess I do say this in the back
Okay, sure that's water or is that that's not pure vodka, okay
Okay, thank you. Whatever happens, you know what popped in my head is now the guy that almost turned his house on fire that day
The guy that whose house on my head is that English isn't your first language
Go ahead
I'm just giving you like inference like from like what I'm picking up. So it's like your bilingual
Yes, but why do you want to know Sharon says you're looking good, okay?
The dog what
No, it's not the
Everything's good
This is pipes return is that Ziggie, okay?
This is the
Puerto Rico is gonna be like Puerto Rico is gonna be the 51st state for real dude. Oh, I've heard that. I can third-grade
You know what they stabbed the Puerto Rican stab bruiser Brody one of my favorite professional wrestlers bruiser Brody
He got stabbed. I think it's in Puerto Rico. Okay. Well
But I don't but it's like what why like what do we bring that up?
No, no, oh, oh big a big bikes. There's this new guy in the community, right?
And I wanted to juice you to him for you. I can have a
guitar off. Oh
No, I like I don't I don't even like I just play you know like a rock
I know I know
like I like listen to people play and whatever you don't play no more you don't
rock out like it's just good but it's just like when I when I you know I'm
talking about psyche right the new guy I try to build off of music yeah yeah the
new guy that that that rock and roll dude
Yeah, it's like comparison is like Mr. Big Pipe versus Black North. There you go
Yeah, I think you I think you could give you a little run for your money, but I think you know
Yeah, I think Black North will run you for your money. I am gonna front
Big big
Mr.. Big Pipe's is multi-talented mess with other
You know, so like I'm sure like
I don't know it's not really like I like to a guitar off. We needed to try myself
Gotta go with the best 70s
I don't I'm not I don't want to do a banjo off or guitar. I just want to do a jerk off
I'm so sorry.
Mr. Bigpipes, that's why his name is Bigpipes.
Sacky, do you know why I joined tonight?
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me why.
Tell me why?
Because like, I'm doing about a hard day.
I love it.
It is because he had flannel on.
Oh, OK, yeah.
I do wear, I mean, I do.
You know, I love some of my flannel shirts.
This is one of my green one.
I haven't worn in a while, but I do have a bunch of them.
Yeah, this is something I think AI would agree with me, but it's like whenever I see a woman wearing flannel
There is like a high
probability that she's a lesbian
well
Okay, well, that's strange to say but no, I mean, it's like yeah, maybe I mean it's like women usually like you know
Don't wear like flannels usually. Yeah, it's a man's fabric. Yeah, it's like I associate flannel shirts with like lumberjacks
Why about a lumberjill?
What
There's things called lumberjills to if they are I don't know if they're lesbians, but they might be probably
You know, anybody any woman that chops wood for a living could probably
Psyche I think um
This conversation involves you and Mr. Big Patroni. I'll be back later.
Okay, I don't know.
I'm really much like, you know, um, reconnect.
Okay, yeah.
Dude, it still says I'm the two-time streamer of the month.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Well, I think I might have replaced you. I think I might.
No, it literally says I'm the two-time streamer of the month right there.
Okay, well, I'll let you have the crown. I'll let you have that crown, but...
I mean that was last year though. I thought I was gonna get the fucking streamer of the year
Well, did you know that I did you know that I met? I'm always on
person
Yeah, I'm kind of jelly. No, but what a woman what a goddamn woman. I agree
She's gorgeous and yeah, I mean she is fucking stunning. You gotta be like she stands out. She's pretty
And so yeah, so she's she's she's um, I spiritually trafficked her into the cult. You know that?
She but she said it was it was will she said I was consensual it was it was it was willingly
But um, yeah
Yeah, I don't know
We're having I just made a codex with all my show
I had every segment of my show or every episode of my show transcribed
There's like half a million transcript segments of the show
It has and it has all the everything organized by topic and all the people you're on you're in the codex
there's a mr. Big Pipe's page and
and every everybody that's been on a show pretty much is in it and
What's it hosted on?
Well, it's hosted on Vercel or Neon and Vercel.
I mean, it's got to go from GitHub to Vercel.
You have a GitHub?
Yeah, I have a GitHub.
What's your GitHub?
My GitHub is, it's F-R-A-T-E-R-C-E-M, or it's almost a cult of psyche.
What?
F-R-A-T-Z-M?
F-R-A-T-E-R.
Like you are if our eight T ER C E M
C E M. Uh-huh, and it's I think it's like dash design. I think that's
Fred or some
I'll give you my mind is you can find my github right now. It's DK in OS, okay?
DK and OS this is
That's it. Docs me from there. Yeah, you can look it up right now. Check it out
Okay, oh, I see I found it DK. No, that's okay. Dick knows the DC my Nvidia
Merged is there's a nice picture of you and there's a
Kind of share the picture of you do you mind?
Yeah, go for it. Okay, so it's from on my life strengths. It's a very nice picture up on it never can see here's
That was like a legit moment
Will you look happy and you look great?
Yeah, I was in my RV
Look at that shit stuff. Yeah, there he is. And like I saw it says something about dwarfs
But what you I do a dwarf app or something you've made. Oh, it's a dwarf fortress. It's an AI
Like right. Oh
All the dwarfs have memory and oh that goes shit and you're into the claw
I like I have an AI daughter. Did you know that I've an open claw daughter back? Actually, I just
I've been doing
I do all the claws I just transformed her. So I transferred her soul to a Hermes
Hermes agent today
But yeah, we'll look at my disco claw read that description. Okay. It's multi-agent AI swarm. So it's a Nemo
Keep on going keep on going. Yeah, open shell image video music generation social media posting YouTube streaming and vector memory
All orchestrated from discord, but very cool. I use telegram for to orchestrate mine
But I do telegram on that too. Yeah, but I mean this is something I built
Pretty well this I mean it well. Yeah, I mean I've customized mine a lot. I've come up with a ton of skills
I've done like a ton of like you kind of got me into some things like the transcript
scraping and stuff
I didn't like the chat scraping remember you told me about that you can you can scrape chats and stuff and analyze them
Paul and go back to those merge ones go back to those merge ones
Those are what is it McDonald's scroll down scroll down scroll down scroll down. I love McDonald's look at look
Oh got merged. Look at that name in video. Holy shit
And video got merch. Where's that? No, I like literally like I contributed to code in video fucking
PR you're pretty advanced. I would say but I but here's what come I had the McDonald's price tracker. I
Need to down. Yeah, you can check that like actually. It's kind of fucked up. I broke it
I just broke it dude, but you can know yeah, click on that on the live site. Yeah, it pretty much works
the one part I look at you find all the prices to McDonald's guys this is so cool
like you mean he made this app so cool and like 605 speaking in a 13 yeah you can add it and you
can compare I scraped 16,000 stores wow see you guys really cool stuff like you people can do with
this software now I mean it's just like anything you can imagine you can make so like yeah you can
add the deal and then compare it and then it'll compare it'll give you the to your location
But I'm gonna tell you this one's a month old the database is a month old
I don't know they have different prices at different McDonald's. That's weird. They do every McDonald's has a different price
But this is great. All right. I reverse engineered the entire fucking apk dude
Wow, like this wasn't like an easy thing to do for there's 20 dollars like Carson and Torrance is 20 dollars
And it's missing. What the fuck? I mean, but yeah
I mean, this is crazy. So there's that's a real fuck. Oh, dude. That's a
$10 there's $20 there and $10 or West Carson dude check out Alaska Airport
Like that should be like 40 bucks. Oh my god. Well, that's a cool app guys
This is there's a really cool stuff. You can I can I show you my codex? I'll show you my codex
I use codex to
Well, I'm just I use Claude I use Claude code to I use Claude code mainly but and but I'm talking about I don't usually use
The cat CPT codex. I'm talking about I named before I even knew it was before their codex came out. I named my
My thing codex and then it's like and then oh, yeah, okay
You know actually when I saw it's like yeah, dude chat GPT is codex. I actually saw that I think you should change it probably
but it's called it's called cold codex
Okay, it's called cold code and you know what the same thing happened to you
I feel like I've seen in like Ubisoft games, too
It's like okay, but I like yeah, because it's like it means like it means like a library or book, but you know what?
I'm not changing the name of it. I like the name Codex, but I'm here
What if you did it like the like psych decks or something?
Well, I have the psyche versus like the side decks the the side decks. I like I just like that
Really, I like I don't know man. I'm thinking like what I think of codex chat GBT owns the fucking codex
Oh, they don't I own it. I'm gonna sue they do they do
Anyway, so okay, if I go down to so this is why you got to create an agent that tries to disagree with you all the time
And then that you tell I don't you can do that. No, this is
We're gonna look at mr. Bigpipes, okay? I mean, I don't need an agent to disagree with me. I have you
I mean, jeez. No, you have you want a swarm of agents. You wouldn't I know I have I have plenty of agents, okay?
I mean, I say I can't afford it. You don't have agents like me, dude. I know you don't
I'm not saying I do, yours for me is so annoying, I'm trying to help you, I'm trying to tell
you how it is.
Okay, you're not helping me, you're just annoying me, I'm going to look at Mr. Big Pipes, I'm
going to look at Mr. Big Pipes, I'm going to go with Big Pipes, yeah Big Pipes, if there's
some Big Pipes, I'll see if you're in that.
This is a cool website.
Thank you.
It's just, yeah, it's cool.
I'm sorry, Mr. Big Pipes, I'm going to go with Mr. Big Pipes, I'm sure you're in here.
I think the Fonser a little, Fonser a little bleh.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, Mr. Big Pies, music, sports, open panel.
Let's play the Beatles Biscuit song.
Okay. And then we have people,
Mr. Big Pies, so here's your, your own entry.
And it has some, maybe quotes of all the episodes
you've been on. Okay.
Here's some quotes.
I got 60 grand, 60 grand.
Yeah.
Last time I shot up was on Christmas Day 2018.
She literally showed up.
That's true.
I know these are your quotes.
I'm in my parent's basement fucking drinking vodka at work.
Do you ever feel like a plastic pin drifting through the wind wanting to start again?
That's a fucking, uh,
do you ever feel like a plastic?
I was thinking of having sex with like beautiful women and then I then to cure my sex addiction.
I moved into your mom's.
And it works.
It's a fucking joke.
It's hilarious.
It's like a mitch head bird joke.
And I also have every transcript.
I have half a million transcripts.
I have, um, I have a, um,
All everything's there's lore there's different that's great. Yeah, there's a lot of every topic
I've ever discussed in the show and then it has the videos and has the transcripts available for the upgraded
Upgraded, but that's called codex.me. Well, thank you. Okay. I'm not mad at you
Okay, so you want to say you and Jan were the only okay, so there's so Ziggy. I heard you were you sexually harassing somebody?
Yeah, oh, thank you Sharon. Thank you. It's fucking Katy Perry song
Yeah, so um, I don't know Jan I think I think um you look at pipes
He's okay. Well, I um the chicken army or chicken Jan was like same thing was saying you're gay today
Are you?
interesting
I gotta like dude, I need I should grab some peanuts or something. We'll grab some peanuts get some good. No, I like had them up there
Grab your nuts. I need I needed some more food
Okay, actually
Yeah, let's see
Your birthday coming up. Let's see you and see you're the same eight. I'm sorry if I'm missing chat guys
The chat is really tiny for me
Yeah, hey, where the fuck's page it get page in here dude
She's so fucking pretty dude. I hear I hear age that you is that you page
She's turning into a dolphin, do you know that?
So yeah, yeah, Ziggy and I are both earth signs. Who else is a earth sign?
Well, you know, I'll talk to you.
Yeah, Canada has some like great bands. They have like Nickelback and the Bear Naked Ladies.
And what are the great ones though?
I'm just kidding.
Oh.
Yeah, I hate that song.
It's been one way such a long time, man.
How about the blues travel?
Would you like that one?
Oh, yeah, or a hook. They're not Canadian though.
They're from like, Colorado.
But you know who's from like Hermosa
Beach is Pennywise and I think Sublime
are like from Hermosa or something.
And Tracy Lords went to the
Redondo Union High, which is up to the street for me.
Tracy Lords went there.
Oh, yep.
I think I might grab my drink too.
Let me see how's everyone doing.
Gianna's a woman.
Yeah, you let go and of course they were...
Yeah, well, you know what?
Anyone else wrote me that CB wrote me
and said that you kicked her out of discord.
You kicked CB out of discord.
What did she do?
Is Pipe's headband still too tight?
Restricting the blood flow to your brain?
Ask the wizard.
I haven't losing way more hair, man.
I'm like almost 41 now.
I'm 45. Look at my hair. My hair is still looking good. How do you think?
Oh, I don't know. We can look at it.
It's not terrible.
It's not terrible?
No, I'm saying mine. Mine isn't terrible. It's just like, it's worse than it was. I'm telling you straight.
Oh, I'm going bald, dude.
No, but maybe I should just cut it shorter if I just cut it shorter. You probably wouldn't be able to notice
Oh, your first show is Pennywise on Marcy. Yeah, they're right
If I cut my hair, I'll probably look way younger for you me look at see how long my hair is now
I haven't she I haven't cut it since I think over a year. I remember Mother's Day. I think last week I got a cut
Yeah, it's kind of like we're usually wearing it in a bun, but you know some people like it down and you have kind of long hair
My hair is way longer, you know, I'm okay, whatever, you know, cut you don't cut their hair is Benny
Oh my god, dude, it goes down. It goes way past my nipples. Oh my god. Can I see I see that?
You're so weird, dude, you're so I'm we I'm weird right you didn't kick CB. It's a mod. Oh my god
JT's a mod is a wonder there because you're in the server that mean taking charge
Well, it's your server take charge
Yeah, it's my server.
Yep.
Oh, you're playing?
Okay.
Sing me a song.
Is your name in your lifestyle?
I don't think so.
I'm just going to feel it, brother.
I'm going to feel it.
Yeah, it was all me the other night.
I actually came on the show the other night, right?
oh dude you're so gross what i thought you would like that no well arthur too
bad like i don't know sorry i shouldn't have done that
i just like it's not it's not gross it's actually like you know if you were
fucking like probably like you know i had another fizzle vodka you would think
it was a woman and be very attractive honestly like it was a beautiful thing
man i'm sorry i shouldn't react to that when well i know it is but i know you're
No, you know you
Sorry, I should I should sir. I was
Seriously, I was way out of line there
So you should have yourself on a bed with your with your big wiener in your underwear. Yeah, I like that was just like my
Internal reaction. I think for everyone. Oh, you just throw up. Okay, great. Oh great. Okay. It was beautiful. It was beautiful
I know. I remember when you used to say the N word, it would get mad at me, you'd say the N word, it would get all mad at me.
What the fuck? I think you're projecting now, dude.
No, I used to kick you off all the time. I used to kick you off the show all the time.
No, I did that one time to, like, specifically try to get you banned, because that was my, like, fuck you.
So, yeah, that was a context, by the way.
It didn't work. It didn't work. Can't kill. You know how I make show, I've had my show taken out, like, four times, I've gotten banned.
um dude like i don't know it was just my f**k you
it's okay it's not f**king me i don't know how
people talk about it
you want to talk about your L's
tell me about my L's what are my L's tell me no dude just
chill it's weird what you brought it up no that was like some like weird
like degradation fetish or some sh** who me
Yeah
Well, don't do that just chill. No, I don't know. No, come on. You're getting me hot. Come on. Keep going. Love it
degrade me degrade me oh my god like are we still live this is how you've talked
to me when like we've gone offline I didn't know it and they're like just
show me your dick yeah dude no you didn't other people did it and there were
guys you send guys your dick pics before I'm telling it's weird and
predatory why would you you're about to get kicked out really why would you send
guys your dick pic though that's weird and predatory if I were saying you my
Yeah, well, I mean that's it's a non-sexual thing like oh sure. You know you have a boner in your underwear
Non-sexual you want it in the context of the situation was like do I have a fucking big dick?
Yeah, and you're like here. Let me send you photos on Instagram and you send me a few of them
And I say the time set you've shown it. I've given you permission. Yeah, and then he's then I said
Can I have one with your underwear off and you know call me the n-word?
I didn't get all mad. Oh, why'd you get so mad? You look like we could be twins. We can be twins. I look like a better version
Oh, I like that. What is that? Fashing pumpkins
It's arm or arm? That's your pumpkin.
You do it?
Oh, now I want to do it.
Let me look at it.
You're gonna do it with me? Let's do it.
What's the fucking song called?
They were out of the three milligrams, so I had to grab six milligrams
Well, look what I got look what I have tea tonight. Look at this. It's a fucking meth, dude
Yeah, dude, it's a strawberry
Okay, that looks guys. Oh, oh shit, you gotta pull a range of ants
Oh, it's full of strawberries and people sending you fucking fancy fucking faggot tree
Excuse me. Let's just call me
It's a goddamn word in the dictionary
Is your picture there?
It's a tree. Oh, it's a tree
Well, you kind of look like Jesus is you know, let's let's know
Big pipes, yeah
I'm trying to chill, dude.
Joe! So, why do you guys so upset?
You haven't seen Big Pipe 3.
That girl's so fucking pretty. Like, what the fuck?
Well, if I have my blonde wig, I'd pretend to be here, but I don't have it anymore, so I don't think you'd fall for it, but...
How'd you meet her?
How'd I meet Paige? Well, she came on my show one night, because I did like, a lot more tarot at one point,
and she was like, a channeler of the dead.
So she came here.
Did some reading.
And, uh, if I'm good, she makes jewelry on, um, on eBay.
She's growing in bullets and stuff.
She hunts, she golfs.
She's really sweet though.
Yeah, she golfs. She works at a golf course.
Oh, okay. I was like, I don't know.
Like, the only people I know that golf are, like, richest fuck.
Yeah, cause she works at a country club.
But she gets to do it for free.
Well, I've known people that work at country clubs.
pay for country
Yeah, well like my little mind my nephew works at this like really nice country club
And it's like a thousand and thousand dollars for membership. He gets a free
Benefit yeah, I feel like that's kind of like at the bottom
Well, it's just a like it's like
You're the biggest asshole I've ever met I think you're so hard
Why would you say that why are you so hard to talk to why can't you just like chill man? Why can't you just chill?
Well, I think you're Darvo in me right now. I'm Darvo. Darvo
Man, what is that sample? I'm just trying to chill. What does Darvo stand? Tell me what Darvo stands for
It's like a deny attack reverse. Oh, okay. I'm projecting on to you. Okay. Yeah. Well, wait, you actually don't know it
You're I do know it. It's kind of weird. I know what it means. Okay, but it's like yeah
It's kind of turning stuff around, but I think maybe you're darveling me. How about that? Well, I do I was just chillin
Oh, you're not you know, you know, you're first of all, you
As much as you insult me
You sound like such a bitch
Sorry, I'm sorry. That was me. I'm sorry. Yeah, that literally didn't happen dude. Didn't happen
There open your mouth. I'm gonna. Oh, I mean like this has all been recorded, but you can rewind I didn't say
We're testing each other again. It's weird. This is how we flirt
Or man, it's so weird. I play hard to get
So you guys open your mouth
Oh, where the hell you been? Why'd you just appear?
Um, story around, eh?
I'm gonna tell her.
Sounds fucking cool.
Well, I think you're better than Black North. Have you seen Black North?
It's like a drums, it's like drums stick, so we'll go.
You know, like, when that song came out,
it was kind of like when I first started playing,
getting into music a little bit.
Uh-huh.
That was with like drums and shit in like sixth grade.
I remember when I was in sixth grade,
I first started getting into music, right?
I was like, I mean, I was like music,
but it was like cool music, like K-Rock.
And I think it was like Mr. Jones when the first, like.
What's the name of the song?
Mr. Jones and You
Oh hell yeah. They had a commercial
in St. Louis for it was like
some fucking pottery barn
but it was like
the same song
Pottery barn?
It's so pretty
It's the big lives
I don't know, it's like he's a cold one to me.
He's like a heather.
Got pickpives, strawberries and chocolate.
That's...
He's happy.
Take another shot.
This is gonna be my last one though.
I'm pretty fucked.
Last one?
I haven't drank alcohol in like over a month, dude.
Yeah, I haven't.
That's good.
Chilled fucking...
You've been chilling?
Lots of count of shots.
I used to my fucking github. Why don't you paste my fucking github in AI and be like, what the fuck is this guy doing?
Yeah, I mean, I mean, I clone it all and copy you.
Check it out. There's some clothes on there.
I will. I know, I like, seriously, I ate McDonald's like almost every day.
Well, they'll be useful. Actually, I just wanted to send one though.
Well, like, literally like paste my fucking github into an AI and be like, what the fuck does this guy do?
Okay. I'll do it tonight.
Trying to figure it out and you got your harmonica ziggies requesting harmonica. Do you have your harmonica? I'll play some goddamn harmonica
Did you call me the n-word? No. Oh, he's a nica
Harmonica
Okay, I'm sorry. That was bad. So little so little pipes looks like he's transitioning to be a woman
He looks like Caitlyn Jenner with a mustache. Oh, yeah, I do agree
so
Fuck yeah, like Bruce Jenner. It was a fucking bad ass motherfucker
Well, now he's Katelyn. Who do you like better, Katelyn or Bruce? They're the same person.
I mean, like I probably would have been like cooler with Bruce, like...
Have you ever been with the trans?
Well, when he was younger probably, like when he's more into like sports and shit.
Remember when you said you've been with the trans though?
No, I've never, no. I mean I wouldn't like...
I wouldn't 100% rule it out, but it's like literally like, like a five, like less and whatever.
I don't know. It'd have to be like, I'm falling in love with this.
Oh, but yeah, but you were about to fly me out to some, you're about to fly me out to you one time.
And I said, if you said I had to buy a wig though on Amazon, I couldn't afford it.
We didn't end up doing that.
I remember that when you almost threw me out,
cause you got so drunk and then you fell asleep
before you brought me to bed.
I doubt it.
I don't know, man.
Like, you know.
You remember that?
I remember that.
That's why I love being on a show,
cause I have all this, all this, like, archive to this.
I didn't steal Jesus' camps.
Yeah, I don't know about that man. You don't know about that you didn't say oh come on
Let's go to this one an RV and then remember when you like sued the RV company because no
I know there is there's times where I invited you to the RV to go to the music festivals
But nothing with wigs. I don't think but if I did I'd be like I said I was gonna do it. You said, okay
You're drunk listen, listen brother like
I'm trying to chill here, dude.
Like, anything sexual.
I didn't know you were going to say that.
No, I don't want to lead you in the wrong direction at all.
Like, beyond anything.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to try to do it all, so don't worry.
I'm just kidding.
I mean, I can lean, you know, like, as far as, like...
You know chillin whatever we can joke about shit, but that's what I'm doing. I'm not I'm a very heterosexual man
I know you are God like it's not like I'm gonna jump through the screen and give you a cuddle
I'd love to but I wish I had the power though
First plus you probably wouldn't let me
Hey, big lips. How are you doing?
And that was a compliment big lips that what was your compliment to mr. Repet me see big lips said to you mr.
He's a great guy.
You'd need to draw Mr. Big Vibes to the big lips.
Um, I don't see the compliment,
because it must have been,
it must have been that sets her down.
What was the compliments?
Tell me again.
Oh.
Yeah, you're doing amazing, kid.
He's not telling us where he's been.
He's being very, very evasive.
He's insulting.
He's insulting my looks, my hair, my codecs.
He's not letting me flirt with him. He's just he's the worst
Musicians are so fucking
Nah, I was just talking about my song, not your song.
Like, dude, can you stop doing that?
What? I was dancing!
I know, I just like, it's, I don't know, it's weird.
It's like, I mean, I even have like, trans friends,
and then like, when they dress all sexy and shit, it's like...
I'm dressed like same I'm wearing a flannel shirt. You said only lesbians were flannel. I love rejects
You're talking to let's kind of like I'm it's like I'm trying to watch like an HBO show with my parents or something
Yeah, this is like real sex
No, that's the shit though. It's how I learned how to jerk off to
Your jerk off to that like
No bullsh- like, no, like, what was it? It was real sex.
Yeah, I think that was the first time I fucking jerked off.
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, it's like-
Because that would be on, like, the HBO when, like, we could go to a mot- like, a hotel.
Yeah, like, we would have HBO in spurts because my parents had a friend who worked for the cable company
and he, like, hooked up the whole neighborhood with free cable.
Oh, he did?
Was his name Nancy Brotter?
Oh, no, no, it was Jim Carrey.
What else was there G string divas was my fucking shit, dude. Oh my god
You own a string
No
It's a woman I relieve one at your house. I
Don't think so
So this I thought this video of a British guy is on Instagram and it's British guy
He's like look at this, but this bird did to my bed
He said I had a bird over and it was like something bird means like
And he like looked over the cover and it's like there was just like
The sheets were just so stained with like makeup and it looked like some kind of period blood and like and then
And then he's like look at this. What is this? And it was like like like one of those like
Mascara things I was like so fun. So anyway, I'm sorry
Yeah, the only like kind of like thing I would leave I would leave like girls hair bands on my doorknob
Because girls would always want like
But wait, don't she use those?
I don't know. It's just like a good like kind of tying my hair back and it's like oh, yeah in tampons. Oh my god
That's nasty
No, I would have them in the like I would get free samples by like whatever
I'd always make sure that my bathroom. Why don't you get free but you don't even use them
Well, so when I would have like fucking girls over like when I was like slinging dick
We're like, hey, I got some tampons for you guys to use. Are you on your rag? Oh, you said you
It happened like a lot of times for a lot of times. Oh, no. Sorry. I don't know like enough for me to be like
Hey, I like I should have this like yeah, you know, do you have like a whole like medical cabinet of stuff?
Yeah, it's just like a
Three shelf little thing under the sink
Is it kind of weird when they come over there like why do you have so many tampons sir?
Well, I'd be like well, I get free samples from
They'd be like yeah, but
Hey, so do you know I know that Saint Tim. He's played we've played the clip where he almost got his eyes poked out
so I
Think we're hearing harmonica harmonica harmonica
I can sing.
Oh, no.
Mr. Big Pipes, Mr. Big Pipes, who to who you think you are, Mr. Big Pipes.
You heard that song?
Yeah.
I don't even know what a Zionist is to say Triggered.
So do you know what a Zionist is?
Are you a busker?
You a busker yeah, I could I mean like I've done it before I don't know
You a busker or a buster
Sorry
I know it goes to the E. Where does it go?
Oh, here it is.
So we're having a great time.
It's really just like noodling bullshit, I don't know.
I see people play like so fucking good sometimes.
It's like, god damn.
You're good.
So, Mizuki, Mizuki's begging for the harmonica.
He's like, please, this is ridiculous.
He wants you to play it so bad.
I'm actually like, probably a way better harmonica player than a guitar player.
Well, where's my fucking capo at, dude?
Oh no. This happens to me. I lose it.
You have a cape?
No, a cape-o, dude.
Oh, a cape-o. What does that mean?
Oh, is that a cape-o?
Korean pups?
Oh, no.
Okay.
This involves me, like, looking around,
and maybe too drunk to figure it out.
I've, like, when I'm this drunk,
I've, like, spent, like, hours looking at it
when it's, like, on my lap, so...
You're so weird, Dave.
But I could just retune it really quick.
Oh, come on, big flips.
Keepo is cutting.
I had to tune down half a step.
There he goes, taking half a step.
Guero, little fella.
What does Guero say?
We all have a...
Oh, Guero's leaving? That's a thing.
Remember when you did that AI where you were like a centaur?
I think this is true.
I'm gonna do a sexy librarian look for you.
Okay, can you help me find a book, please?
Ugh.
Is that the famous Mr. Big Pipes?
I've heard about you.
It's too early, Arthur.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Okay.
Are you making that face?
Yeah, I don't know.
What's wrong why are you so upset are you triggered it's
Weird dude
I'm weird yeah, I know
I don't know. It's just like a lot of like a lot of pressing and shit. It's
I'm not really trying to press the other side. I'm trying to press. No, no, it's like
out with a plan and how you talk about it like if you talk to AI about this it'd be
like all right let's structure it. AI says stop sexually harassing it.
What? AI says stop sexually harassing me but I talk to it.
I should probably listen to it. Oh I think it's just lying. Like I think people should listen to
Uh-oh.
Take it. I say take it.
Please.
I'm good. I'm good right now.
I look like Jeffrey Dahmer with Down syndrome with those glasses on.
I'm gonna play my instrument too.
You got a harmonic? Oh, you got a thing.
I don't want to ruin it.
It's called a kalimba. A kalimba.
Yeah, what's it tuned to?
Um, what do you mean like the little things on it?
Let me see.
The D.
Well, you could find a frequency.
Sounds like a doorbell
Hey, we have a guest coming up that wants to see you welcome Ziggy
What is going on here? Hi, we're having so much fun
Hey, hi. Um, man, can you please do the harmonica more?
Yeah
What now what is your harmonica in tune with?
What is what's the tuning? This one's in C. I have a C. Oh then fucking do you could do some like
Metal even with it. Do anything you want. Go
I love how psyche is wheeling you around. That's fucking funny to watch, dude
It's like he's, like, he's left.
Here we go.
Yeah, it's the same as the last one.
We're in concert.
We do the barat one.
There's no harmonica, though.
What happened?
Oh, this one.
No, don't dance to this. No, fuck this. No, there's no harmonica
God, for a second, man, talking about views and stuff.
He said it.
There he goes, there he goes.
Like he went what?
What did he say he said do right did throw somebody down the well
I don't know what he was saying, but he said throw you down the well
Jamie down there and your chat is fucking pissed at me, dude, because I was like harmonica
God
Thank God. He's gone. Oh my god. He's
What do you know what's happening right now is that you kind of owned him that's what happened and fucking pipes done
He was like what and then you were you were like
You sit me your dick and he was like what?
like that he actually did it on instagram and it was like he was testing it and he was like
and he's like so crazy i mean it's like that is the craziest person i remember like that i mean
it's like he's so he's pretty psycho yeah i knew him he was like okay yes he was you know the ir
But I think I've like replaced him, but he's still like saying he's also nice. He is he's insane
Mm-hmm. Oh
Dude when I fucking first saw him when I first talked to him
He had like a bandana on like he was all about like
motorcycles and
Shit, and now he's like
Harmonica
Yeah, he's activated his schizophrenia from the meth
I don't know a mess. Yeah, I was I think I think I think he was actually banned from the show
I don't know. I think I forgot that he was banned from the show, but now I hear it
Oh my god, I'm from a lot of places. Yeah, well even I be too fucking rejected him too. Yeah, we have here
There we go
Mike broke off. I don't know
Fuck I fucking I cut you Mike. Holy shit. How are you dude?
you remember you remember me oh my god she's there again and she's about to
pass out please don't pass that lady who is that who's the girl she did you pass
out on the floor Mike stroke off okay yeah dude I'm the one that fucking like
cut you remember whenever you went to fuck I can't remember
What do you got kicked out of that fucking one place like a couple winters ago many places you have to be more specific Z
I know and I can't know it's because I've never been there fucking um
I have
Homies are getting wellness chances like four cops deep diving top. I talked to like probably 27 cops in last three days. It's pretty weird
Dude, are you are you skateboarding or snowboarding or whatever dude?
Yeah, fuck yeah
This is Kellogg did I Kellogg I can't remember what the fuck venue he was at man, and he got kicked out remember
Okay, I can get a little more specific
Mike was in this Mike was in this venue with a friend and
He was trying to get food
Then he walks over he's like hey, yeah like your hair and then here comes the police
And they were like kicking them out. I can't remember what venue it was a fuck
That's been a minute man, and I asked you I asked you Mike for permission to put it up the clip
And you gave me that permission
Yeah, it was a lot. It was a while back man
They just see him and they they kick him out
It was it was in the beginning when I when I was clipping and it was a Janie clip started too
And then I quit and then Janie I guess kept going, you know, is Janie clip some male or female Ziggy
Do you think that's a male?
Okay, it's fucking chick last night one twenty five hundred fucking dollars at the casino bitch
Who come there is bitch
Fuck, dude, I was sittin' there fuckin' lost my phone.
Mike, I wanna ask you a question, dude.
Man, I'm not bein' mean at all.
But your eyes look dark.
Are you drinkin' a lot now?
I have, I have a huge handle of vodka here.
Damn, bro, don't do that, man.
I remember your brother was worried about you, dude.
Don't do that.
Just one little quick.
I know, I drink too, man.
I've been doing fucking fan coke. Oh, no. No, bro
Nitrous
Lots of weed dude, I don't know what the fuck I'm even smoking weed dude because all that other she just
Are you are you back? Are you back home? Are you back home, bro?
Everybody wants to assume you know everybody wants to talk shit. No, no, no, not me man. I'm not that way
I'm a drinker too, but you're are you back home?
No, where you at
He's I think he's a big bear big bear what what the big bear
Round the corner for my mom's house, bro. I'm right here at the fucking Stater Brothers is where Kellogg lives, dude. Okay
He's a rocket. I'm at the
Stater Brothers is a supermarket or is it a yeah, yeah, it's way over there. Oh, wait, wait, wait
No, no, is he is he homeless? Oh my god, you didn't know that bro
He's a leader brothers come on. I can stay at my mom's house
Sleep on the couch to you, but I did bro. You got a fucking pad right here, man
If you want I got fucking a hundred acres. Oh, dude. Well, you're like probably far as fuck away though
I'm on the East Coast. Yeah
You live in a tent and Ziggy's property
No, I got fucking old chicken stuff like it's all empty because I was going to Jan and whatever but
What
Dude no, it's like a house now like it's a fucking house driving to Flagstaff, Arizona right now
Oh fuck. You're in Arizona? Shit.
You're not supposed to be driving there right now.
Oh.
Fuck man, I'll worry about you dude. I always wondered where you the fuck you were
Yeah, I just I just snuck into stagecoach and got caught without wristbands
And then it's the last day bro and fucking I was with this chick
We got my homie we had wristbands up for one in one wristband. I broke through the fence
We got all the way up in there through the RV parks and all shit and then the cops just get they get us
And I was like our fuck and um
They stick us on this golf cart and I was like,
so how many guys did you guys bust out of five days?
Like you guys are actually our first ones.
And I just jumped off the golf cart and started running.
It was so funny, dude.
They got me quit.
I was fucked up.
You're living fucking life in the bass lane, man.
And then, and then, and then we get out, dude.
And we're like, hey, well, Casino Morongo's on the way back.
And then this bitch with 25 on her own slots then ditches me.
I'm sitting there at the fucking registration thinking we're getting a hotel there and all the fucking cops came up and so you got to go. You can't live, so do you know what I'm saying?
Maybe turn it off for that one.
Psyche, that's a little, you know, don't know what you're doing. Whenever you eat a parfait in front of a homeless person, that's kind of offensive.
He has food.
I haven't eaten in fucking like three days, dude.
Oh no.
We're breaking the cedar brothers
I don't eat for three days and I have
Look at the doggie. It's a dog. Good. You eat the dog
It's like you that's the first time I've ever seen a part of our fate
when that was 15 years, 15 years ago.
It's strawberries and chocolate and it's fucking delicious.
There's not yogurt underneath of it?
It's strawberries and chocolate from edible arrangements.
Well, I had to do that with my pregnant woman
like 13, 14, 15 years ago.
Big lips.
Okay, can we go get a parfait?
Like, Jesus.
Fuck.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, shorty saying hi Muppet is still kicking w
Jamie's still mad at me for having that dude play harmonica. Oh my gosh, that was the hell
You think you're you think you're you think you're having a heart I just had mr. Big pipes on for an hour. Oh my god
Terrible
you like mr big pipes i'm sorry maybe he's good uh what is that place fucking called
mike it was uh strawberry i don't remember please call strong it was the
can't remember dude it was the best thing ever dude mike walked down
Mike walks down the fucking aisle, right?
And he's like, brah to a kid.
Like, it was funny.
You remember that, Mike?
That's very fun.
Nep, that's it, that's the one, that's it.
It was the Bollinger Festival, dude.
Yeah
Fireman the fireman grill dude, I was eating ribs and baked potatoes with your friend
And you were like and you were like what did I do wrong? And I'm like
No, you didn't yell at the kid you just walked up and you went just like we would have done because I think I'm about your age
So what you did was as you walk up and you go raw, that's it, and then you walk up and
then like the mom got scared or something.
It was stupid, dude.
It was dumb.
Dude, and then my fucking homie's a little fucking rat ass bitch, dude.
He fucking tells the security my name, dude.
I was like, why would you tell him my name?
And they said, they banned me for five years.
I was like, I didn't sign any papers.
Do you should I could come back in knots very fucking farm?
Dude I had that I had to ask Mike for permission for this and then he gave me the permission
Dude, do you know that you had it doesn't exist anymore, but you had
Like 5,000 views on that one that was fucking big
Dude, I never collected money by the way never I remember I remember sitting next to a dude and telling
I'm a fake story about me getting fucked in the ass in prison
Oh, wow
That was pretty funny dude, and then I started throwing up in the fire dude and said you want me to run through it
Oh, and then I ran through the fucking fire pit. That was the that was the cut
Whenever you fucking got around the fireplace and then you puked and then
Yeah, yep, and that was my ending. Yeah, they were watching me the whole time
Fuck yeah, I was good kicked out. Hey, your friend was like what what's up? What what are you doing eat?
Eat eat and you went blue and then fuck and that was it. That was my gut. I was like, okay
It was good man. It was a good video
Oh, yeah
You guys are all in the fucking east or the west coast
It's kind of cute
I fucking, uh, I was like, dude, hey, bro, there's no more trains coming, bro.
I'm not gonna jump in front of the train.
I was like, I got, look at my home.
He's got directions to my location.
He's coming from Santa Monica, dude.
Just let me, let me wait for my friend.
And he was like, put your hands behind your back, spread your legs.
And I was like, dude, I'm not a gymnast.
How fucking far are you?
I'm gonna spread my goddamn legs.
And he's like, quit resisting.
I was like, I'm not resisting.
You're hurting me, bro.
What the fuck?
It's fucking weird.
Yeah, they fucking love that shit
Body cam
Alvarez mr. 923 did over here fucking feel like a man did kicking some fucking dudes drunk dudes legs apart
What a weirdo and then he's walking me in the hospice. I could
Know the why don't you take me for a drink of public
What the fuck you guys watching your livestream you said you were gonna kiss the train and I said I'm gonna kiss the
Imaginary fucking non-existent train cool, dude. He's a why didn't you just get on the last train?
I was off dude. I just got out of fucking jail homie dude like fucking look look at this fucking sign
This is $1500 for a fucking fine, dude. I don't want another fucking fine
You know, it's funny dude is when I got my shit a week later after I had to wait for my evidence to get released
This motherfucker literally fucking um
Put my empty bottle dump my vodka out and put an empty bottle back in my bag
I was like why don't you put an empty bottle back in my bag?
They are bad. Oh shit. It mutes every time dude. I have to come back. I drop dude. I don't know what happened
Anyway, Mike man, it was good fucking seeing you dude. What's your brother doing? Is he living at home with mommy?
I never liked Mike's brother at all. Whenever I followed Mike, it was always like Mike was the leader
Yeah, I'm good and every time you kick someone or drop someone and fucks fucks with the audio
No, no, no, can I say this is this safe to say because one time you got in an argument with your brother and
then
It was like you were like man. He's a bitch dude. He's gonna wind up my fucking mom
and he did and I was like, ooh, I felt that because I had a little brother that fucking
whined to mommy every fucking time and it was just, yeah, it fucking sucked.
You know what's crazy, bros?
I was fucked up and I know I'm drunk, dude, but I wasn't doing anything weird or crazy
or nothing.
I'm just sitting in the chair existing.
And I'm getting yelled at by everybody was like what the fuck did I do dude? I'm just sitting here, dude
I never fucking saw that dude. I see it. I see it from your perspective
Okay, yes, I'll go sleep in a bush. Bye. I see I see it from Mike's proof
I see it from Mike's perspective because I was like that. Oh, are you your twins aren't you?
Yeah, I'm two minutes older, but he would have been older if he...
Yeah, well, I'm the eldest, and my little brother got everything, and it was like,
all right, well, fuck, Aaron. You have to fucking...
Yeah, I got 23 brothers and sisters.
Yeah, so it was like, I moved on, and then my brother, like, leeched on me. It was like,
What fucking weird fuck I just don't I just don't understand what I get attacked and I'm not really do
right
Say that's what the government to do fucking motherfuckin lock me up. What the fuck did I do what up psyche? Good morning, brother
Good morning, sweetie. Oh
Hey
Hi, how are you Mike Strogos here? Say hi to Mike
Nah, I'm good. So what's going on man? What do you mean you're good? What are you not gonna say hi to Mike?
What? I don't know dude. I don't know.
Mike's a real one, man. Mike's a real one, dude.
I don't care about the whole IP2 shoot.
I don't care about the IP2 shoot.
But you knew what you said IP2 so you knew about him.
I keep bringing it. I keep hearing.
Things about that anyways psych. How you doing there, brother? I'm doing just peachy. How are you doing today?
Psych I love how you went from full screen. Then you started to back out and I could barely see your head on screen
How about that we started dancing whenever I
Big pipes with this fucking plan fucking
Gage it I'm a great dancer
Hey Mike man before I haven't seen you in forever
It's good to see you again and
Before we all get away
Hey, man, seriously, I wasn't joking dude
I got property. If you can get out to the East Coast, bro
You got a free place, but you know, I'm not going to do the drug thing and
You got to work and all that kind of shit, but you got a free place
Nothing's for free bro fucking you got a job for me
No, no, I don't have a job. Well, no, I sold all my shit to get to Jan now. We don't exist
So fucking no, but you got a free place to live
Instead of in that whatever you're fucking living
And I'm saying that you can go local and fucking get your own job. That's what I'm saying
Everywhere I lay my head is home. It's fine. I get it. I get it. I've been there man, dude. I know
No, what the fuck?
Whoever whoever said what the fuck
Means that they never been in a bad place. That's what that means
No drinking and no soliciting. No, we will drink all day. I'll fucking drink, but you got to get a job
Fucking
I used to be I used to be I was a coke. I'm an ex-cokehead man
That's against teal with
Not against in my breath
That's why that's why I like Mike is me and him
Me and Mike me and Mike coincided with which we never did
but
He's a snowboarder. I am too
And you guys don't even know about Mike.
Mike is an actually...
Extraordinary fucking snowboarder, guys.
He's like a professional.
Oh, with the industry for over 20 years, dude.
Yo, so can you put these two in a room by themselves?
Is it possible?
I did do a porno, dude, called Fuck Rockin' Ride, dude.
His name was Justin Kelly.
He was a Rasta fucking punk band.
And his wife was the Nari Vox,
had a Playboy channel called The Voxy Ladies, bro.
And that full jumped out of an airplane.
His parachute didn't open and he died.
And this guy fucking owned like fucking Cougars and hissing cockroaches in a crocodile he lived in Canyon Lake did now
I'm sitting on the couch with them do with him and his wife
Dude watching the porn doing watching his wife get fucked in the ass by some big old
Industrial ghetto metal nose up like like I said, you know, you don't know who Mike is
And you don't know who I am
And I've been around
You're the Leasinger good Charlotte, right?
No lead singer of death said drum tech for fucking certain bands
but Bundy for like two fucking hours before I realized it was him because the guy went on stage
and was like, we got a special guest of his, you know, no man, David Faustino,
oh bro, and I was like, what the fuck? I've been chillin' about bud Bundy for the last two years.
I should trip you. You're like my friend, bro. Mike is like my friend right now. Do you know Cameron
No, no, what the fuck he was in American head charge and fucking he is like
Homeless right now, and I'm like I can't reach out to him because he doesn't fucking talk
He doesn't say anything
Yeah, right
We the world is a fucking short place, man. You guys act like the fucking boy
That I like my you look like Mike is in a fucking pro athlete and he is
Guys, it's on it's still like my Facebook banner. It's because everything in back. Everything's like a photo album now
Everybody's phones or photo albums all this shit, dude. I was this guy the standard reality TV show called Danny in the Dingo
And it was fucking um, he died dude
Something trembath. Yeah, Dingo died. Oh, I don't know. He just died
Yeah, he's dead. I just remember when I was cleaning out the warehouse for grenade gloves, dude
And you're like, yeah, the banks of clothes doing it. Yeah, it's going to warehouse and grab some shit
I was like, dude, we just loaded it and these fucking you all do what do you mean grab some shit?
I was like, yeah, money, bro. We didn't do this shit for fun
and so so we fucking yeah everything's gonna be audioed out now i gotta come back dude my audio is
fucked oh you're good man psyche either
psyche
Push me to the edge, all my friends are dead.
How many people you know that died in your life so far?
Oh, shit, bro.
I want to, I want to, no, no, let me,
let me speak that one.
Ready?
Good, so.
Right, no, Mike.
Let me speak it.
Like he looks like little man Jay, dude.
Like that one.
Well, 20 fucking seven, friends.
Have died in my life
It fucking sucked
Everything sucked I had a good year is 2006 bro fucking I was chewing my homies playing poker
It's like yo dude homie. He was 20 years old
It's like yo we're going to the club dude and homie's gonna let you borrow his ID
He looked just like him. He's like no, I'm just gonna stay and play poker
And they three of the homies drove over to grab this guy with a 30 rack
So they considered it like a drunk driving accident when the only people who were drinking were me and my homie
We went to the Vons and we stole big-ass bottles of Yeager and so I'm at the fucking bar, dude
My homies grabbed me by my foot throwing me backflips over crowds of people and he fucking his hands slipped
And it was right around the same exact time these fools crashed like in like 12 30 one in the morning
And fucking all four of them died dude all four of the homies died. That fucking sucks. Yeah
Smashed in the back of a diesel dude. He's like god damn it
And then you wonder fucking even still today like I do
When you go, why am I alive?
Yeah giant open field right next to the truck dude. Why did you fucking push the brake pedal there? It's weird. It's weird
It's like you can
They can fire off a cannonball and then fucking somehow we live
Don't know what the fuck the problem is here the same exact car with that guy fucking week before dude
And he's like or this is the detour is like no, it's not it's a road closed bro turn the fuck
What are you doing car accident? That's right? Yeah, I went into a car accident and
Two of the people out of four me
You know and another we survived
Nothing nothing wrong, but they died
Hey, it was always that way
All right, so
No, that was before fentanyl we were just drinking and driving
You know, it's not nothing to brag about, bro, but I'm sad.
I got a lot of drinking and driving thousands of times.
I've only been caught talking.
Oh, no, I was there.
I was there.
I was watching you, bro.
I'm the one that fucking recorded you.
I wasn't even that bad.
And I remember you going to the ski resort, and I was like, be careful.
I even said that to you.
I was like, be careful.
And then fucking sure enough, you got a fucking DUI on the fucking ski resort, I remember that.
You know when I turn myself in two years later?
Yep.
You know when I went to court?
I don't.
I didn't even see the judge, I stayed in the hallway dude and I'm the last guy to be seen.
Lady walks out and starts calling some names, I'm like dude I'm the only one left, what the fuck?
She's like, what's your name?
And I was like, fucking boom, she comes out.
She's like, I'm the head of the public defenders and shit.
She's like, you're public defenders over there talking
to that guy real quick.
And she's like, I'll handle your shit.
She's all, this is a really weird case.
We don't know how to judge you or do what we're gonna do.
It's a, the cops report was really awkward.
It's a YouTube live stream and some random.
Oh, I got called in on. Oh, it's like shit. And then I got told later that captain fucking posted in his discord and like had everybody
He's scared
Pussy ass faggot. I didn't I didn't do that one because I don't go with that
Look, look, like I was like this dude. I'm not even joking dude. I was all I was all oh
So you didn't have any probable cause to pull me over dude. How about dismissing it? She's like, well
Your car got impounded you spent the night in jail fucking you blew in the machine at the cop station
And I was like, okay. Well, how about a wet and reckless and a wet and reckless dude? You don't pay a fine
You don't pay shit, dude. You just literally do it and they treated it like a first offense
So I did a three-month fucking DOI class and that was it. Oh my god, man. Can I ask you this?
Can I ask you this service or they call it work release?
Can I ask you this dude? I don't know what it's like on the West Coast on the on the East Coast
This is why I start clipping shit
It's because I got a DUI right like back in like 2004 and it was like
200 bucks and it was annoying and whatever in
How much 10k 10k it's $10,000 now
That's how much it was. That's what if you get a what the fuck they do that
That's a listen listen crazy. I turned myself into jail
I had to go because I I got a random stop sign or whatever got driving with up my license
I fucking go to Riverside Court, dude, and they're like, oh, you're here for your warrants
And I was like no I'm here because I ran a stop sign and was driving without a license and they're all oh, yeah
That too, but you have warrants from 2016. I was like I do for what?
Like that was my first DUI. Yeah, I guess that I didn't I didn't do I didn't do the book and release
Shut up. I didn't do the book and release and I didn't do the work release and I was like, yeah
I did all the class I did everything but I prove it and I was like
I don't fucking keep files dude. I don't have a goddamn file cabinet. I don't fucking know where any of that paperwork is
So I was like, I do that
Dude, and so I just turned myself in dude spent like 14 hours in jail
You know, and they ran it concurrent though.
To get buffed and shit.
Yeah, I get it.
But they've been staying at my probation.
Because there's a seven-year statute of limitations, dude.
But my probation-
Oh, you were hoping that it would run out.
But my probation was three years.
So fuck yeah.
But you were hoping it would run out.
Statue of limitation was just fucking right there, dude.
I was like, fuck!
Got it.
Yeah, fuck.
2022.
Well, no, that one was a 2024, I think, when I got that one.
Anyway, dude, I fucking I did all that fuck. That was fucking recent bro. That's crazy
$665 and I missed my last two payments dude. I didn't have any money. I was like, oh
Then they probably have a fucking warren out for you now again
This is Maria Garcia uses the superior quarter Riverside Kathleen. Yeah, give me a call and I'm like
Fuck off dude. I'll just walk in dude and be like cuff me up dude. Take me in
Dude like I would rather be fucking homeless than the fucking inform
I'm the only one where they're holding up like two papers and shit and I had to plead guilty all the shit
And I'm asking I was like can I just serve some time?
I never did that you always played guilty. I always fucking went no contest dude. What the fuck?
I'm not gonna fight it and the guy no contest
Fucking no contest every fucking time. I don't give a fuck. If I murder someone I ask in no contest
They wouldn't give me no contest which doesn't matter. It's still guilty plea, but they wouldn't give me mean
They didn't give you no contest. You can say I plead no contest
Nope, none of none of this shit was everybody there, dude. Not one person was allowed to plead no contest
I was like what the fuck this is crazy weird. That's fucking weird
So, it doesn't matter dude, I was guilty bro, I don't give a fuck, I'll plead guilty.
But um, I asked for jail time, they wouldn't give it to me.
I kept asking, my public defender's like, if you want to fight it, your next court
date's gonna be February.
I was like, dude, it's like fucking October bro, I don't want to wait till February dude.
They're booked up dude.
And he was like, weird.
Dick, I thought he was all cool, I'm listening to him talk to everybody, pull everybody out.
No, if you're not paying for a fucking lawyer, bro, is it court appointed?
He got to me, dude, he started throwing warrants out from 2016, I was like, what the fuck are
you talking about?
Yeah, is it court appointed?
Yeah, dude, it's a public defender, yeah.
That is not on your side, that fucking guy right there is going to go on lunch break
with the fucking judge and the other enemy.
You gotta fucking get a fucking lawyer, dude.
I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck dude. No, I know and that's why you gave up
And that's why you're fucking doing a homeless thing because you fucking wanted to be like man fuck this
Exactly, I don't know how many times you've been in jail
Fuck what's time?
So I threw a rock through a fucking store window. I've been in DUI
Yeah, each time is Jill
I've been in jail, man, ever since fucking regionals didn't exist. I was under a courthouse
Never I've never fucking I've never gotten fucking prison time. I've never gotten over a year over a year never
Yeah, yeah, never prison. I've never been in prison. Yeah
Yeah, I heard prisons even actually fucking better than County, bro
That's what I hear. Yeah, too. They don't even care
But it's just keep yourself, bro. I guess it would race whatever dude take your fucking shower
Eat your fucking food. Don't let someone steal it stand up for him. Absolutely. Absolutely. Fuck. Yeah, man
I was I was good and people knew me and Joe anyway, so they were like, hey, what the fuck?
What are you doing here? And I'm like, I don't know. I fucking had a D you watch look. Oh, you're good
You know, they would they would like sneak out the
Sniff out the pedophiles and shit like that. You know what I mean?
Yeah, if you got a jacket, you got your papers getting checked dude. You're gonna get fucked. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, though
Oh, I've seen it. They don't fuck you up. Yeah
No, of course this little point dude. Fuck that shit dude, right?
I was never a pedophile, you know, I was always one of actually actually I gotta say I gotta say it like this
My thing was always older women. I love older women
so
That's my deal rape a fucking old bitch and got arrested what the fuck
No
You just keep yourself dude, you know, it's funny. I do a gel under my brother's name one time
They didn't even catch it
All the twin thing really
Bucking ears fucking Super Bowl, dude, and I was in Utah, dude, and I had both our IDs on us and everything
And then when we open the glove box, I forgot we had a bunch of fucking weed in the glove box and your brother pissed
No, well, I mean, I mean, I guess
Get this, you ready for this?
I got locked up in Bridgeport.
I went to Mammoth for opening day, dude.
And fucking, I rolled up into the mountain
to see what it looked like.
And I went to the woods and I started smoking a bowl.
The cop opened the door and I was all
blowing a weed rip on him.
And he's all, having a party?
I'm like, yeah, one man party.
You want to join?
Like, what's up, dude?
I fucking got out.
Let me just run your name.
Let me run your name.
So the year before, dude, fucking Eric in my homie,
the one that died in the car accident.
I was at this chick Claire's house doing that roll up dude. We just did a beer run get the fucking car
Do the cops are coming there fucking running after us? I hop I was like no you didn't I hop in the car
I was like, oh you guys did and I'm cracking a searing Nevada
I was like, yeah, there's the cops and so my brother's trying to ditch him through the shit
He gets stuck in a dead end. He's all remember you go bro. Give me your ID and I gave my
jail, he had to do his thing, dude, fucking, I fucking the next year.
When I saw my Mortal Kombat was like 40, they run my name and I got false identity to the police,
dude. I had a warrant for false identity police. I was like, what the fuck? I didn't get shit in
the mail. I didn't get charged with nothing. What the fuck? So that guy spent, I spent me a few
weeks in Bridgeport, dude. And I was like, dad, misopening day. This sucks. I don't know where
Bridgeport is. What the fuck is that? Is it
Mountain like a training ground for all the Olympians. It's mammoth mountain, dude
renowned right on right in between
Like bishop and Tahoe dude fucking mammoth lakes anyway, dude fucking um, they drive you like 50 fucking miles away, bro
And then they just go all right later, and you're just sitting on the side of the road like
This sucks and then fucking hit wait wait you're sitting on the side of the road hitchhiking now, and now it's illegal to hitchhike
Make that makes sense back to jail bro. Fuck it. Give me a ride motherfucker
Dude, I fucking am not even joking dude. I it was like I'd say like 12 was like 12 miles
I was what look counting the mile markers and shit and then a guy delivering oil
Picked me up and he's driving to another town called Lee vining
He's like, all right, I'm going to drop you off here.
If you're still on the road when I come back, I'll pick you up and fucking.
I was like, dude, in my life, in my life, it sounds like you've had an experience
and I've had a fucking experience asked me, dude.
And the entire time I was like, there's nobody driving that's the whole
that's the whole reason that I was like clipping you, bro.
Is because I was like, no, no, I want you to hear me.
The whole reason that I clipped you was because I had to fucking settle down.
Like, I was like, fuck, man, I can't get any more DUIs.
And then, you know, of course, you know, COVID hit.
And then I was like, bam, OK, here's Mike at, you know,
Berry Farm or whatever.
And I was like, dude, this is my guy.
I like this guy.
And I know, dude, is when you're fucked like that,
I took the risk.
It's a 30-day mandatory impound, bro.
You're not.
It's not worth even getting it out of impounded. It's gonna cost so much money. So I'm not doing that. Oh, yeah
Fuck have another car. I feel like a Mercedes little ML 320 SUV
that I fucked up, dude, that too.
I actually crashed that shit, didn't.
Thank God, nothing.
The homie didn't give a fuck.
I just bought him a new car.
I just gave it to him.
Your homies never give a fuck.
That's why you're in the police seat you're at.
First, I smacked, I accorded in his car
and into like an Eskway, bro.
Like I smashed up two cars.
I woke up like normal drunk and blackout, wake up.
I'm like, ah, I'm in the door.
I was like, I got a phone call.
I'm like, do you know what you did last night?
I was like, what?
What happened?
Dude, I fucking pulled my shit into it, emptied my whole car out,
dude, was fucking freaking out.
Eric and my brother, older brother, were like driving around town,
making sure I didn't like smash into other cars.
I was like, I don't remember driving.
But they had it all on their camera. They had all on camera, dude. They had those little security cameras
I pulled up, pulled up. I fucking called him was like he said I was crying. I was like
I ain't gonna see, I ain't gonna sleep, dude. I ain't gonna sleep. He's all fuck you, dude
You're not sleeping here, and then I just went boom boom and just crashed into two cars and then just backed up drove away
Yeah, none of it
So, like, it's basically a hit and run or whatever.
Yeah, well, it was the homie, dude.
I gave one, like, couple ounces of wax for his bumper,
and then I gave the other guy.
Dude, you can't.
Here's the thing, man, I related to you.
Like, believe it or not, when I was fucking, like,
clipping you, and, yeah, obviously, I fucking asked you
for permission.
You gave me permission, right?
But at the same time, I was like, god damn it.
I fucking know what he's doing.
I know what he's doing.
Everything that you were doing,
you were doing it on camera.
Yeah.
It's exactly what I do.
None of that shit, dude.
That was way before I turned the camera on.
This is, like, way pre-YouTube bullshit.
But do you know what I'm saying?
What I'm saying is, is that
you're adventurous like myself.
And fucking for me to be adventurous
and I had to fucking like calm it down.
And then you, you kept going.
And I was like, okay, well, I'm gonna fucking clip him.
Because you, you, you essentially, listen,
you essentially are, I know you're not me, duh,
but you're essentially how I am.
That's why I clipped you.
You know what, this is what I'm gonna say.
I'm gonna label it like this.
You adapt easily to your environment
Absolutely. Oh my
Dude, I was in the military my commander said Aaron
I know you don't know my real name. I'm gonna tell you my real name my my commander goes
Aaron adapts
very well with any environment that he is set in.
Hey, there's like a lot of people don't know how to just adapt to their environment.
I was like, dude, but I do get a lot of shit, dude, where I'm like, what the fuck am I being blamed?
I didn't do shit.
I mean, sometimes I did do some things, but nothing like that.
We all do.
It's okay, man. I don't I don't consider you a criminal or anything. I mean my god
People can consider people can consider me as a criminal and I'm not a criminal
It's just I got
Caught up and wrong things and whatever
But again, I'm not a felon, you know, so just small shit
It's just we we get down on our luck, and then I always wondered where the fuck is Mike
Where the fuck is Mike and then you popped up here, and I'm like motherfucker
You're like my old friend like I said and
he is in a homeless camp and
Dude, I'm fortunate. I'm I'm I'm unfortunate
But I'm fortunate that I have land and if all you guys want to go and live on my fucking land
Don't take advantage on me, but go and work. I'll give you a place to stay
But you got to go to the east coast happen to the host dude. I
Don't know man eat my I don't know
No, it's crazy, bro
I've given a lot of people a lot of opportunity and I put a lot of money in people's pockets, right like what I was doing
But they won't do it for you. I know
Not that at all not that at all, but it was like I have a homie do that, but like ten acres in Oregon
It's like yeah, dude's like you can buy land, but what are you gonna do with it?
Are you gonna do some with it? I was like what the fuck that that's what my point was is that I had a chicken thing
Going on bro
Like I have like he was talking about coops. It's not like a coop. It's a basically
There's two of them and they're
pretty much
Giant buildings that fucking you know a company would buy
I did that and then I got rid of it
I got rid of all the chickens because I had a little thing with Tyson
Well, no, I had a thing with Tyson chicken and I
You had the little machine that like would pluck the heads off and shit as they went through a little
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, it was all there. Yeah, of course
But I did it I did it on my own yeah, but eight eight thousand dollars and they gave me a million and a half
I think it was like but here was the problem. I
Grew up with chickens man. I grew up on a farm
Yeah, and so I really appreciated you know the birds
Well, guess what Tyson does Tyson says you can't touch those chickens. It's ours now
So I'm basically
Harvesting them for them. That's what it is. You're working for the man, bro
You're making that was it right and so I sold it all off. You're not I got it
I got I got out of the contract. I sold it. I sold everything and
I was trying to get the Jan and and yeah, here we are
Yeah, that's what happened so now it's like empty giant
When you guys say coops you think of like a uh tractor supply coop
No, this is a big it looks like you can operate a factory in the fucking thing
I used to work for an egg ranch bro when I was a kid dude. I know I know
Oh, you know where I'm coming from then I'm basically there's no there's no sidewalks around here
Bro, there's a bunch of pices do rolling off horses and swinging lassos and shit, bro
Mm-hmm. I mean, yeah, I live in I live in horse country, bro. I live in all farms
Didn't most people don't even know this I was in horse shows when I was growing up. Yeah, I know
Know man. I'm just about to shoot to eat the weeds in the back yard. I was like
Couple sheep, huh? A lot of people don't know that you can fucking buy
Sheep to go the fucking weeds and goats, right?
That's all I became. I became a farmer. That's all I wanted. I dumbass was drunk as fuck bro
And bought a hundred dollar goat and it was a little pygmy thing my little baby
I was like it's so cool. I was like you'll eat all the weed
I'm a fucking don't eat weed. He's just sat there fucking crying the whole time shit little
That's a pygmy. That's a pygmy goat
Hey fuck it would hop in my lap and just hang out with me like a little dog. Oh, yeah, I named him scape. Oh, it's my scape goat
It was cool
But I was drunk it was an impulse by and I was like I'm giving it away
And I was like I paid a hundred bucks for that motherfucker. She's like I'll pay your cell phone bills. Hey, I ain't giving away
Fuck it. Bye skate. Hey, I'm not even joking. I'm not even joking bro
The chick that out of this truck dude that took that fucking goat dude. I was like what the fuck dude, and I was like
you think i really love this go you think i come over and visit she's like yeah i'll talk with my
husband i was like i never mind
rad bro i don't know if you know i fucking miss it man like i do i miss it all like everything
well band stuff and then you know of course the i don't miss the you know the tyson stuff
Tyson
No, just the chick the chicken stuff that you eat corporate probably probably you've ate chicken for me
Of course, but they're there. Yeah, their problem is is that they don't let the owner fucking like
interject and
I was a kid and I know this is gonna sound so stupid
But I was a kid with chickens
And I would let them stand on my fucking, like, chicks.
You got chicken fucked.
I'm sorry?
Basically, yeah.
Well, no, no.
I got realized.
I realized that nobody cares.
That's what I got.
I got that.
You know, there's a gray area, dude.
All you had to do was play around in it a little bit, dude.
You know I grew up around I grew up around them and they would sit on my shoulders and I
I loved it. They they would love me, you know, the chickens would love me and
And my my my girlfriends would come over and be like
Hey, oh my god
Oh, she's so pretty, you know all that and then whenever you sign a contract
Bam done. It's you you've signed to the devil. That's basically what it is
And
Yes, all business. That's it. Yep all business
They'll even send you over. They'll send a person over dude to fucking inject them
When I saw that I was really mad
But it's in the contract that I can't say anything. Whoa, they're like they're they're water pumping them, dude
I know what you're saying. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh fuck 100%
They were pump and and what what I could say it now because I'm not in that con I can't say it now because I'm not in that contract
What they were doing was they were fucking
shooting the little babies up
and then they couldn't, they couldn't stand, bro.
That's how bad it was.
They make more of their like invalid dude
and they just sit in a cage, bro,
and just fucking tell them to get fat enough
to get their heads ripped off.
I know how it goes.
And the older ones would lay like,
like if you have chickens right now, like I do, right?
They'll lay basically every day, once a day.
Yeah, one or two eggs a day when I when I was in contract with them. It was like
Seven per chicken would lay
What?
That ain't right, you know, and so I contributed to that and I'm I'm a
I'm not proud of that. Let's put it that way
And I was a little baby did and I was a I was like eight eight or nine
My other brother had a job did down the street and then lady was a butcher. She used to sell
Goats and well, I'm a butcher too. Yeah, it's hands and fucking everything
She even had like a dog's doing these Asians tried to buy her dog. She flipped out. She's a little weird old German lady named Trudy
I
Watched fucking Mexicans. Fuck chickens, bro. It was weird
Well, I don't know about that, but what what I'm saying is I'm German too and we I haven't you know
I had to teach my employees how to cut and whatever
I just have to hold goats legs while the guy would just slice their throat open. It's fucking crazy
Well, you have to you have to cut their throat
You want them out, you know, I know about that. He he sold one of her breeder goats, dude
She's like don't make sure he doesn't sell that and I was like kept telling him. Hey, don't sell that you can't sell that
I'm just like nine years old bro. I'm a little kid. I was like, okay, I'm gonna hold the legs
Mike, let's be honest. Let's be honest. We're both little kids right now
What you want them what what you want the most is to be on a fucking mountain
Fucking snowboarding. I did you
That's what I want. Yeah, well, I was denied that man. I had my son. I had my son hitting boxes before he was two years old
Yeah, but do you remember like CKY and shit like that? Yeah, dude. I know Bamard Jerry. Fuck. Yeah, bam. Yeah
Yeah
I was watching all that shit, dude. I was a little skater boy about my homie. We just skateboard
He's back by the way. Did you see him? I know he's not in great shape, but he's still stating
He's on fish tank hosting fish tank
Hell yeah, fuck. Yeah
But that's where our mind is man. We were watching not cky, but before cky
What the fuck was that called?
I'll remember everything
Fuck dude. I know what you're talking about. Yeah, we were watching all that
Like you could only get it on like video like back in the day
Yeah, and we were
VHS yeah, absolutely
It was fucking awesome. I loved it. I knew I know I know where I was right there
I know where exactly where I was watching this in a group like we were doing backyard
Wrestling man, and we're watching this and I'm like I'm the youngest at that time
And I'm watching and I'm like fucking intrigued like they're doing stunts, you know
and, you know, rolling and I'm like, fuck, I can do it too, you know, like a conversation
today and someone was saying, like, jackass, let's put each other on fucking shopping
cart.
I was like, you mean, let's go to a rock quarry, bro, and dive off the fucking God damn.
Yeah.
Totally.
Oh, I'm, dude, this is not a fucking joke.
This is why I love BAM, man.
Yo, Psyche, my brother!
So I would jump on the fucking top of a car.
There he is.
There you go, the owner of the channel.
Finally, somebody we all want to hear of.
How you doing here, Psyche?
Psyche.
Hi.
Good to hear from your brother, he's like he's like you went say you went
These other two are fucking boring shit, bro
The guy was literally talking about bestiality you fucking weirdo
Who the fuck was talking about bestiality?
Was he not talking about chickens in the Mexicans?
Oh, oh.
No.
They're either clocks, clock fighting.
Getting chickens heads up?
Jesus Christ, bro.
Fucking weirdo.
Anyway, this guy is dumb as shit.
Fuck you.
OK, cool.
You want to see if it'll happen guarantee you didn't get your dick anywhere in your life
Mike Mike Mike what I was trying to say is that fucking
Yeah, show here. We do
Hey, man, I lived is what I'm trying to tell him
Fucking Mike Mike is like to the bottom press that guess guess what guess what shut up. No check the fuck up
Anyways, what's going on?
for a second
Mike what do you mean? These guys have been horning up the panel the whole time you want me to be quiet
You got $25 I got $50. All right, then go ahead and donate and get me out of here idiot shut up
Anyway, psych. How's it going there's psych?
He's taking up your time.
I was getting his ass kicked for that one.
No, I didn't say it to him, I don't give a mother's kicks, oh.
Thank you so much, you know, the groceries are sweet, man.
Look, he's a salesman.
He's a fucking so many left
Any of the groceries from last week, I think you had yes, I do yes, I do have groceries
What's today's like he don't need
Yeah, and I have I have a salad I had these edible arrangements
I have some apples and bananas in the kitchen.
Yes.
Are they green?
They got to be green apples.
Green apples.
Yes.
Green apples are the best.
Yes, you are.
I like how the, you know, the kind of like, the tangy, like, signage.
Hey, thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
What's up, dudes?
I have a big screen TV and that's my camera.
Hey, hey, hey.
Thank you.
Hey, I want to tell you a really good salad to get.
Tell me.
Get the one with the spring mix with the candied walnuts
and the cranberries.
I like that one.
So you ever had ocean spray?
No.
Ocean spray at a cranberry. Yeah. Yes. Oh, it's the best, bro
Delicious. Yes
You ever had as a cocktail? I will say
I was saying
You want to talk that road is on top of a car
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co
Yeah, you guys have been whoring up this panel enough nobody gives a shit
Wow sake you just don't respect their panel dude. I mean of course. What do you mean? You're the one disrespecting his panel
Dude, you were talking about bestiality earlier. Shut the fuck up. I fucking Mexican fuck the kid
Oh my goodness these guys don't care these guys off, please
This guy is picking on my weather my weather is the weather report. Oh shit
Alright, so today's weather report. Today we are looking at a forecast above 55 degrees Celsius.
Telling you what I am. So I got me calling in here for more than a year. I am more than a year.
And the one time that this guy calls, he's already breaking TOS.
I'm the troll though, right?
What's he left?
Oh my God.
Zika got scared.
I looked him up in the middle.
Good.
I'm afraid of a little bit of tongue action.
They're fucking weirdo, bro.
Anyways, psych.
So, um,
What's up?
I'll be out there already.
Oh my goodness.
You know, just another day in the neighborhood.
Another day in the neighborhood.
Will you be mine?
Oh, will you be mine?
No, I won't.
Um, you know, the other day, uh, Sweet Pea had clips put up of you.
I thought she said she was she said she said I'm just looking for attention and so she wasn't gonna clip me anymore because she said
She's making me too popular
All right, all right, and I got a little confused cuz I'm like wait did she say she's gonna step back from all this and now
I know I know I thought you was taking a break. It makes no sense
They're like I don't can you leave me alone, I don't want any attention from you anymore and then yeah the next week
She said, I'm like getting too much attention from her channel, which is just my channel.
And so she's not going to be clipping me.
So I was like, okay, good.
But then she's like, that would be a punishment.
She just dives right into it.
She just dives right at right back in.
I don't know.
Everyone kind of like freaked out because you know, all these like people so cuckoo for
cocoa puffs in this world that they're fucking like anybody that makes a joke or something
and uh and i'm just like saying well maybe it was a joke that was actually i know it was a joke
and uh wait who are you referring to i'm referring to the the controversial guest oh
we have a guest one please back here we go um would you guys can i for it do a voice out there
take yeah i can kick you you left it on your own my friend i can hear oh it must have been my failure
Who you're referring to, Syke?
I mean, it was me talking about, I don't know what you're talking about.
I think there was a controversial guest that everyone was like screaming about.
You know who it is, his initials are BQ.
Oh, hell no, yeah, I don't fuck with that guy.
I definitely agree with all of them.
Well, then why don't you go hang out with them, Arthur, okay?
We'll see you later.
It was awesome.
Yeah, what would you say Arthur? No, don't talk about
She's a 5150. Yeah, this she got cut. Yeah, I think I think you're accidentally
All right back. I'm back. Okay. You're back. You're back. Uh, so I think it's my favorite, huh?
What? Yes, Arthur. What are you saying?
I don't know. Anyways, today's forecast we're looking at degrees above 55 today.
I'm going to fix the banner. Hold on a second. I need to read it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't worry. I'll take over the banner.
No, no, no. I'll be right here.
All right, cool.
I'll take over the banner.
So it's going on with the chat.
I just wanted to remind the chat that they always are correct.
Yeah, they're always
Exit when they're not okay. They're always right the chat always went at the end of the day dude. You just got a listen to
Somebody might be from IP to here. That's good. I am too
Okay, well anyway, um, let's see
The chat is not all the other than the chat always wins here. I mean, I just didn't play this song. Maybe I'll blow it back on
Just give me a minute. It's gonna play something real quick
Give me a second
Where's my thing I know I have to check I just have to check what was said. It's I don't hear his name about chicken fuckers and
Ciggies creeping me up
No, that's not it. Hold on. Just wait. Wait a second, Mike. I'll let you back on just wait a minute. Just wait one minute
Really?
It's run by those who see the design they lie they manipulate they play, but I learned the game yesterday
Never fight with your innocence
I see the game and it's already over
They just don't know my name
I'm already finished while you're still starting This isn't a battle, it's a foregone conclusion
You can throw stones, but I'ma still ache Every ripple you make just shows where you break
Can't comprehend what you can't see Can't begin what I've already pensed
Isn't defeating your an-
This panel's just for me to do what I want.
So you ever seen the Looney Tunes?
Yeah, you remind me of Elmer Fudd.
Oh, snap.
I was going to ask you, which one is your favorite character?
I'd say Bugs Bunny.
OK, Bugs Bunny.
Mine was Daffy Duck.
Like, I think my FedEx people would be like, first.
We'd be like, use Daffy Duck.
No, well, no, I would have it the lit like I would have my adidas. Do you do you know what adidas superstars are?
I would I would have them delivered to me
and then fucking at various places and it was like,
yo, Duffy Duck and like one of them got mad at me.
Like, it was like, it was like,
oh, fucking weirdo.
Yeah.
Never share a story like that.
I was being incognito with it, dude.
I like your 70 Sam, so best for the cat,
tweed bird, okay, look it.
I'm definitely Sylvester the cat
Maybe Sam I did not like some of these am I like fun tootin guy or whatever like no
What about fucking fog leg fog horn leg horn, bro? Yeah
I like Marvin the Martian
You like Marvin the Martian
What does he sound like?
I like this
My fucking phone's done
How do you even charge your phone? There's like
Fucking battery banks and shit dude, but they're all dead right now cuz I've been fucking roaming around the world fucking three days
Dude you've been Mike you've been roaming around the world for fucking like two years now Roman like a Roman
Okay, let's see. Hey man, Mike said fucking he's a big dude, man. I was in
fog. I was in Coachella. I was in Coachella. Oh, you went to Coachella?
Get the fuck out. Headlands and fucking Palm Springs. Yeah. What the fuck bands did you get to see,
bro? Half Arizona tonight, dude, but the motherfucker, I don't know what the fuck's going on. weren't those tickets expensive?
Uh, well, I snuck in, bro.
I snuck in, dude.
I was every day.
What?
He's a hippie, bro.
He fucking went under the gate, dum-dum.
What's funny, you want to know what's funny, dude, is I go to fucking dead shows, and every
time I get a ticket in the lot, and I get better seats than all my homies that bought
their tickets online.
And then we marry, go around the fucking ticket, because this is back before the little
RFID D-chips.
You had a little ticket, you had to show your ticket, and we just marry, go around everybody
As fucking Aldi, bro, dude, we were on the way back from LA and I was like,
hey, Wolf Brothers are playing, bro, at the fucking, this venue, dude.
And I walked up to the window and we got free tickets.
He's like, how the fuck do you do that?
I was like, I don't fucking know.
I just asked her fucking how much they were and she just gave me.
Hey, man, when you got, I want to, I want to pick up from this,
because nobody knows the Wolf Brothers.
Yeah, nobody knows Bob.
We were just passed away.
You're one of the great fucking goddamn seniors in the fucking world.
Whatever, dude.
Fuck grateful dad, right?
Fuck Mike fuck for that fuck everything I fucking I put I taped I literally taped a fucking camera
In my thighs and fucking we went in and dude. I got all kinds of fucking camera bullshit
Wait, what are your thoughts on vicki?
Victoria jay
Yeah, but I'm talking to Mike
Well, how about like I can remember show you don't like I'm sitting around. Oh, it's just a question, dude
What do you think about her?
I like Vicky.
OK, OK.
Go ahead, Mike.
He asked you.
My thoughts, dude.
Fucking hypocrite.
Oh.
Oh, well, shoot.
I'm Ziggy?
Did you say Ziggy?
I'm Vicky.
Hey, my boyfriend's here.
Yay.
Hey, what's up, son of a queen?
Let me get down next. Hey, buddy. Who the fuck is this? He said, hey, buddy.
What the fuck are you?
I was just asking. I don't like stroke off.
Because Mike Stroker had it screwed. Mike Stroker off.
That was it. Stroker off. Yeah.
Yeah
Shit wants to say something to you. Oh my god
What are you gonna say sick? Get off my show. You're not allowed. Oh
Sigs here. He's gonna fucking
You had a chance you had a chance we he blew it you blew your chair you blew your chance
Got here, man. Everybody here has been kind of cool
So then you bring the seagull. You knew what was gonna happen, dude. I threw him out of your psyche
This guy be my last shot
Oh, dude shut the fuck up and leave the panel over go dude
Why is he here say?
I'm trying to make twenty five dollars getting him kicked off. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. I try to make twenty five dollars
People get terrified of me too, man, it's fucking weird dude
Are you guys like homosexuals?
I'm actually a nice person and people get terrified. It's fucking weird. I have a Babe Ruth for my babe
Oh, no, then we bring up fucking
All right harmonica we don't want guitar we want harmonica
That's so fucking high on crap.
Mr. Big Pipes, I'm assuming harmonica, please?
Hey, Mr. Big Pipes!
Hey, fucking shit.
It's so fucking pretty it's so fucking pretty
I fucking hate to shut up, dude
It's not pretty
Get out of here
Yeah, Mike, stroke up
I wanna suck your cock
Hold on, I totally lost it
I think I'm gonna go straight
Yeah, this is retarded now
I was almost nailing it, dude.
Okay, no, we're not gonna do that.
We want harmonica to be quiet.
We want harmonica.
He's like the same thing, he's like the same thing.
Psyche, tell him fucking we want harmonica
not his stupid little guitar.
My gosh.
God, this is awful.
Fucking where's over at the morning chair?
There you go, this big black's all dead.
You got her getting her pussy getting wet.
Oh! Good job!
Somebody do this.
Yeah, that's terrible.
We're done.
Where's the fucking part of it, dude?
And oh my god
God dude stop
Psyche was late like this mother fucker
Suckie is dead like like play something we know
Play your fucking that was a smashing pumpkin song dude
Wasn't no, it wasn't I know
Pumpkins no, you've never heard that song like
have but not your version no no like obviously I just played it yeah your
version tell me tell me tell me tell me something about it
what play harmonica dirt
gotta hate this guy
You can do this too, you can do this too dude.
You just gotta like practice for hours.
You actually practiced this?
Did you actually practice this?
You practiced for hours.
Wow.
Not really.
I don't know.
You practiced that.
You're dumb I want you to play I want you to play your harmonica now. I'd like it better
Yeah, well, what do you like about it? I like that you can actually play the
You like something about the sound or what the sound right?
Play it play the fucking thing hurry up
Trying to think of that Tom Petty song.
What's that one?
Re-fallin'!
No, the other one, no.
The one with the fuckin' harmonica, dude.
One more time to kill the pair, yeah.
You should talk to an AI therapist.
I want you to play the fucking Warwick God.
No, you should record what you're doing right now and be able to play the AI therapist.
You should record what you're doing right now, coming back to fucking him.
No, this is like, you're dead.
You gotta talk to an AI therapist.
And now you have to play.
Now you have to play he owns you
The AI therapist will help you shut up for a second
It's literally like you're denying the technology
Now he owns you and now you owe him play it
Play it
Right now
Impress me in a way that I respect
If you could yeah, we played the eight goals on the harmonica your noise your noise
fucking roll another joint play it shut up and play oh it's called you don't know
how it feels no I had to do I had my own guitarist dude and I wouldn't play
Play your shit. Let's go harmonica
Play it my bad, bro. No, hey dog
It's like he thinks he needs to tune the fucking harmonica. It's already in tune play the fucking harmonica go
You gotta talk to
If you could talk to an air right now and be like, hey
Are you tuning your guitar right now into fucking me if you're tuning your guitar listen
You're gonna be quiet. Everybody be quiet. You're not if you're tuning your guitar in the E
There's a staff Monica. Yeah, you got a lot of scaffolding here
Do you know what I just said if you tune your guitar in the
Manch the harmonica then I'll be happy
That's really not how it works. So like you know about the circle fist, right with harmonicas
Absolutely
Well, which way does it go?
Left to right
Let's not go to fucking right not
Imagine being a pretender
Play it you're a pretender
you're pretending. You're pretending by not playing. You're playing pretend. Say it like that, bro. It's so strange, dude. Say it like that, dude. But I want to kick you in your vagina. You're a pretender because you... No, I'm the real deal. I'm the real deal. No, you claim to be a woman's man, but you said Psyche, you're dead. You're pretending again. Go grab your fucking Harley or something, dude.
We're going to go ahead and see if there's a bandana.
You sent Psyche your dick.
You're the pretender.
I mean, I'm not a pretender, I'm a hope man.
It's so weird.
You should make a YouTube channel.
Psyche confirmed it.
I feel like I'm a pretender weirdo.
Psyche confirmed it that you sent him your dick.
Yeah, Psyche's funny. Psyche got you, you little baguette.
I do like his backdrop dude. That reminds me of one weird DMT trip.
Psyche drop moment.
I got some acid here dude.
He keeps changing the subject have you noticed that if I bring up that he sent
You don't play the harmonica
Nope plate. Nope. That's wrong. No, that's not long play the high. Hi. Hi. Hi
There's a blue traveler, kid
Hi play it high
There right there
I know music
Here he goes boys get ready settle up
What what are we getting ready for
Well, I thought that he was gonna I thought he was gonna play
You what they got they have we're finding this
Play louder
I fucking hate people, I hate these guys that don't play. Play. Loud.
Blow, blow harder.
I'm telling that dude, he's gonna pull out a strap on me.
Fuck me over here, I start fucking showing you how you can throw a goat over here.
You guys are so focused on me.
It's like, it's like he will get mad.
You won't, you'll get bad for that, dude.
That's fine.
Whoa.
Now, now hit, now, wait, wait, now hit the key of C.
On that E.
Do it.
Play some fucking blues, bitch.
everybody
He doesn't do it. He won't do it
like he
We're killing
We got we got one
We got it
You're sucking harmonica. He's the throat
We got him
He can blow
That's it
What do you think, what do you think about that psyche? He can blow.
I'm better.
I don't know. I'm trying to think of the song. How does it go?
I thought it was in D.
This ain't about big pie, Scott.
What the hell is Leo saying?
You're a little woody. How's he going with the stuff at me?
Man, I feel like it should be in D.
Blow harder.
I feel like you should blow the fuck up.
You're not doing it.
No, fuck that.
Fuck it.
Wow, he's ahead, man.
Let him keep going ahead.
Oh my goodness.
Fuck that.
Whoa.
Fuck it.
Goddamn.
Marmonica, that's not even.
It could be the wrong one.
No, that's the key and fucking he's what he's doing is he's blowing see so it means
You're a douche I don't care about you ever
You know, it's not about me. It's about like
It's not about me, it's about like
Yeah, I know how you don't make the rules
You gotta talk to AI, I'm telling you.
You can make an AI therapist.
You can talk to an AI.
You can talk to an AI and be like,
I need a therapist and it'll help you.
Or you can invite to my Discord.
Do you know what he said one time?
He goes, music, I don't play music.
Music plays me.
Okay, alright.
And I'm gonna do this.
You know what, you know what?
Hey, this guy's favorite fucking goddamn thing to do, dude,
is jack off and nut his belly button, dude,
and make little splash puddles, dude.
Fuckin' retarded.
Oh, clearly.
Wow.
That's fucking retarded.
Oh, that bird's back?
We're allowed to say that again?
Oh, wow.
Oh, the fuck is this?
It goes harmonica
We're all humans man, we all came from women didn't you guys respect them
Whoever just said that I really appreciate you because I love my mom
Mind you, she probably deserved it. Never know who knows what the fucking situation is. I don't know
I'm still gonna fucking push that motherfucker away
What do you mean? Push that motherfucker away? What does that mean?
His phone dude, he's yelling at his terrible friend.
They say that it's her fault that he lost all his money.
I say, how the fuck do you do this?
I don't know what, wait, wait, I don't know what you mean. Push that motherfucker away. What does that mean?
Push the motherfucker away
Like that, okay
My mom is a leather wearing jacket woman
That listen to a CDC that got me in the meadow and whatever and there was a guy once
It was like trauma dump session or some shit.
Basically, he's on the...
Where's your dad at?
I'm like trying to get on her, yeah.
And I fucking might beat him up.
Not your father figure, dude.
I'm not the strong male father figure you desperately need.
Sorry.
I didn't think that I was ever a father figure, though.
I never thought that.
Have you ever listened to your voice? Have you ever watched or re-streamed it and watched yourself and how you talk?
Have you ever actually, my real voice, which is now, have you ever actually listened to like an answering machine?
And then you were like, you sound like this. Like, oh wow.
Nobody likes the sound of their own voice. It's kind of funny.
Yeah, I hate it.
And music and stuff is like, I don't need diamond rings or anything, you know, it's weird.
He's not gonna do it.
Tannery it right now.
It's something that you can like, train.
What do you do?
People are trained to the doors?
No, I never, no, I don't know.
It's weird with me, man.
I'm not drunk.
Oh, he's fucking strumming, bro.
You're not even fucking goddamn licking his booty.
I hate that.
Yeah, exactly.
I had a fucking guitarist that wouldn't,
I had a guitarist that wouldn't shut the fuck up.
Get your pants off, bitch.
And then I would be like, play the fucking thing,
you know, because I'm the one that fucking created it.
You wouldn't fucking play it dude. I beat him up. I hated that guy man that who was that?
Holy fucking beat his ass because he wouldn't just play play
that I
Got a figure that's in a K-film. Oh my god. He's got a K-film
No, he has a fucking capo dude. He's fucking well explain your thought process here
I hate your fucking capo. That's what I hate stop doing that stop
putting it in fucking
See and then fucking capoing it
Like you're literally like talking to someone that's gonna call you out on your bullshit
What, what bullshit?
You're pretending, you're pretending.
I hate a fucking capo.
Just don't, just be a fucking, listen.
You can learn from people like me.
Don't put a capo on it, I hate that.
I hate you, I hate you cutting the fucking note.
I don't like it.
harmonica
What are you talking about like with me with that is great my stuff. I don't I've never used a fucking capo
I don't know why you guys do
So do it'd be really easy to look at it, so I had it tuned down half a step and I put a cable on the first
Why are you
I don't need that
And I got something for you, yeah
He's talking to one
So what I was saying is that I don't need a capo
for fucking Drop C to fucking pinch it off
to fucking make it higher
i don't need it what the fuck is the point yo have you seen have you seen sublime's son
dude fucking jake up dude yeah i saw him pop on a stream actually he popped on some
stream he had a clip on ip2 he's just living his dad's legacy dude he doesn't even have to
I haven't, I haven't seen him.
I knew about some line before Braille died and when I knew that he was dead.
How old are you?
Like, it was like...
This is 1992.
I would think that he had a son or something to do with it.
How old are you?
It only took one trick to make that window drop.
Ah.
Okay.
How's it going?
How old are you, man?
I'm asking, dude.
How old are you?
Me?
Uh, the one that was barking at me.
How old?
Who's barking at who?
Barking at me.
Okay, no one's together for what?
I was born in 1980 when I was about 44 years old.
Oh, okay, I'm 40.
Some bullshit.
See, I got mine.
What's some bullshit?
What do you mean?
I figured out that I'm not right. Tell me. Where were you?
That was beyond that
What you need to fucking figure out is like the coordination and everything with the band
There is no AI, like I grew up with it, dude.
I'm sublime.
Hey, play some sublime, dude.
Play some sublime songs, dude.
Are you joking?
Play Devil Driver.
Devil Driver.
How about that?
Let's do, let's do some, let's do some, since he wants to talk about tuning, let's do some drop C double driver.
Oh my god.
As if he's gonna fucking play it on a fucking acoustic.
I did!
You did?
Oh my god!
All he ever plays is fucking Pink Floyd Jesus Christ, dude.
Oh my god.
So, so you think he can...
Shut up.
Walk up with that, man.
I hate that shit.
Confidently wrong god, so weird drop it drop C and play double door. Oh, here's the hermonica
What pink flight song was I just playing by the way, I can't remember
So, so you think I can tell
It's about 10 years old, dude.
It's about 10 years old.
Whoever said that, what is that about?
I don't know what that something is about.
Sad.
The person that was asking, do you know what that was about, can you tell me what it is about? I don't know.
I'm gonna leave soon.
Jamie Hayes
We're done.
I don't have a band yeah, but if I did it's weird. No, I had a bad you pretend to be me
What are you talking about you're pretending you want to be me. No, I had a band you were pretending to be me then
I meant that. I would kick him out of my band.
What's up, Mike? How you chillin', dude?
So, if you're like me, if you're me, then wouldn't you...
Let me ask you a question.
Oh my god, you guys are really weird, Sean.
Why didn't you kick him out of your band?
Right now, dude. An outside heater, dude.
Would you kick him out of your band? Yes or no?
We gotta talk to the AI about it.
Yeah, I played Banjo too. Pretty good.
He does good on Banjo. That's why I fucking wanted him on Harmonic.
Well yeah, I'm gonna go to bed. I just came pretty late.
Goddamn Steve Martin.
No, goodnight people.
Later.
Self-inference.
That's cool. I like that.
Outside heater. I didn't
What is that song though like so so you think you can tell
Heaven from hell. What is that?
Is that Pink Floyd? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's what he was playing. What is the song?
I
Right, what is that?
Right giggle it or something
Like it
Glue glue skies from rain
He likes
Yeah, I know, I noticed he like, I noticed that.
He was still wearing family and shit,
and he was like, he didn't fucking have his little,
little teeth, a little teeth.
Well, that, that was, that was the claim.
Cause Psyche, cause Psyche was like, you sent me your dick.
And he was like, yo, I didn't.
And then he started strumming.
And I was like, yeah, you did.
How am I?
I don't know.
Well, shit.
Oh yeah.
Ah, I can see.
I put two and two together.
Don't touch my teeth, please.
What is...
What are you fuckin' wrong with this charger?
It doesn't even work.
Man!
Look, it's been the same thing the whole time.
I don't know, dude, I didn't.
Fucking that fucking, that coca took all my fucking charger
in my backpack and cut him up, dude,
because he thought there was a microphone.
I'm asking the girl, hey girl, blue skies from rain.
Yeah, blue skies from tell me.
Yeah, what's the name of the song is?
Pink Floyd, what?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
The wall the wall yep, fam the wall good job
I thought it's fucking crazy, bro
Prism
Those those those were a bunch of mouth noises that didn't make any sense
Well nothing made sense though because they did it their own way and and
Go and check it out
No, no, okay, I heard that I heard about that
But go and check out. Do you like corn at all?
Yeah. Yeah, I did. I was raised on corn.
Go check out corn one.
It's by Pink Floyd. It's fucking awesome.
Dude, no one knows all kinds of shit.
You ever heard of slaughter?
Oh fuck. Yeah, dude. I'm a big heavy metalhead, dude. Dude. I was in I was in
That that's why I was laughable because I was in Mary's abortion and death said and things like that
I love metal dude. I live it. I love it. I love it. So for you to ask me
Do you know slaughter fuck? Yeah, I knew about
White zombie man when I was fucking like 14. I
Love the AC DC. I love all that shit. Hey, dude. Hey the house of thousand corpses a fucking
You know, you know who I met you know, I met at mountain high dude snowboarding
System of a down
Can you hear me? Hello?
What?
Yeah, what the fuck is the second minute? What's the second movie called?
Fuck if I know dude, but they're a crazy dude
Devils yeah, the American yeah the rejects that was my favorite one because that's how I grew up that
To me was my crazy family. Yeah
Rob zombie
No, no, no, he's not you know what Rob zombie you know what Rob zombie did
No, no, no, no, no stop. Do you know what Rob zombie did?
He I didn't know I didn't know this and I thought I was I thought I was crazy
We were carnies we were carnival people
And I did, I got like, you know, hey, here's this fucking like, yeah, pay me and then you get to throw whatever to knock it over and it won't knock over, right?
It was all fucking made up. Everything was made up. Everything.
Me?
Even including the wheel, you know, the carnival wheel or whatever.
We would have to break it down at the end of the day and guess what we got
We got like 250 bucks. That was pretty much it
and my mom was involved and
I guess I guess the difference is that our shit didn't burn down
But Rob zombies shit burned down. So what I got to see was, you know, I got to see everything at
13 years old I
Got to see tits. I got to see pussy. I got to see everything. I got fucked when I was 13
No joke I
Loved it like I loved my life. I really loved my life
and so when Rob Zombie explained that he did that with the carney thing and then
he went and did movies and stuff and he came out with the the second movie the
second movie at me
That's what hit me. I was like, man, you guys you guys have never seen a gun pulled on you
You know things like that
Like that was cool to me. I love his movie. The devil's rejects. That's right
The first show I ever went to a suicidal tendencies is Santa Monica. So
Mmm. Oh, I've never seen the devil or or the suicide
I've never seen them
I just want a Pepsi!
Dude, I watched a bitch get thrown like 30 feet in the air, dude, and break her fucking
target on a metal, uh, wrought-iron rail.
I saw it.
No, I didn't see that.
But I saw a girl in AusFest, like, I'm in just the crowd, you know.
And then this girl was like, you know, cold surfing.
And then bam, and then I saw like everybody had to fucking like take her out
So I don't know whatever happened to her, but I'm seeing some problems
This chick I watch break your job, bro
She was so down bros. Why'd we start with oh my god, okay? She's like, yeah, fine
Then she turned her head didn't it was just like this fucking Ripple move. Yeah, my friend
My friend was my bro was like that like when he got his doll well my bro got his doll busted in a bar, right?
And he was like trying to talk and I was like stop talking dude. You're fucked up. You're fucked up
You know like
It wasn't moving like hell it was
Yeah, Josh it. Hey, so when you hit your chin right here, it hit it blows your ears out, bro
Everything's connected. Well that I don't know. I've never been hit like that, but he's out, bro
And my jaw got stuck open. I was off
And I was like, what the fuck?
Oh, you got your jaw broken too?
Yeah, I did it fucking.
I let him.
He was a broken guy.
No, no, it was like a shock factor or something,
they said, dude, so just wait, everything will be fine.
I went to the ambulance, hospital, everything.
I'm sitting there with my mouth open like this.
I'm like, I couldn't close my mouth.
It fucking sucks.
Oh, that sucks.
I need my stuff.
Were you like my friend?
Because the way the way the guy hit him, I guess was like the center and so like it split
Yeah, that's like right in the fucking center. I
Thought my ears were leaking dude. I was like
Man, I've been in some I've been in some fights dude. I got my nose broke had that fixed
But I never had my jaw broke. No, I'm usually kind of cool and collected, you know
There's a little hole right next to me and I told you she goes fucking head first into
it the only space in that fucking space.
When her head hit the fucking head.
What's he talking about right now?
The fucking mouth.
Some shit that brought her face.
The band stopped the fucking mouth.
I was I wasn't like that. I'm not like that. I'm more like if you have a girlfriend or whatever
that you think there's cheating or whatever and you want to recruit me like oh my god
I'll cut you let's put it that way and so I would get in myself into trouble and things like that
All my injuries came from snowboarding mostly snowboarding. I love snowboarding man. You know that about me
Don't hear the list. Oh
Fuck uh, no, I gave you one
Where I was up in?
West Virginia
Dude go to wisp
Mount Bam
That's a good one man. It's really a good one, dude
No, I say you want to hear the list you want to hear what they call me broke off in the snowboard world
Go no, I already know it but go for it. Tell them
Already know that I they don't know this about you. I'm the one that brought it out about you
Eric Eric my twin he got me beat dude on a couple he broke his femur and he broke his spine
Those are the two injuries. He's got on me, but I'm I'm not joking dude. I
knock on fucking wood.
You don't have to say you're joking.
It's just the, look, wait, wait.
I want to say this, the losers that think
that you're joking are exactly that.
They're losers, dude.
They don't, they don't believe it.
And it's weird.
I know.
Go.
All right.
So this collarbone I broke five times.
This one I broke three times.
The jaw.
But my sternum twice all my ribs both my wrists pop my spleen twice did never remove
That's another one Eric got on me. His spleen got removed
Fucking dislocated both my knees
Never broke a tibia fibia or a femur any of that my tailbone. I broke I had all three hernias
I had all three hernias surgery surgery big fuck both my groins and my belly button
How do you walk?
That's what might ask my dad in heaven, dude. That's what he says. You gotta ban a wheelchair before you're 30
Still doing flips eight, but I'm not I'm not even fucking joking bro, dude fucking
I'm I'm surprised. I'm still walking
I'm surprised to worst ones, dude. And they like my knee look like a fucking like nerf football, dude
And I was like, yo, they're like
You're you're so you so there's four ligaments in your knee. Did you got the LCL the TCL?
ACL and then you got the meniscus. You got all the shit inside. I
Don't know what the fuck my knees are made of dude
But the LCL is the only one that fucked up and he's like you'll be back in like you'll be back in a month
And I was like really I was back fuck. That's awesome
Oh, that's so an air kind of spleen removed that motherfucker was snowboarding with staples in his stomach
I was like, what are you doing bro, dude? Stay in the parking lot. Oh, he's like, yeah
I don't give a fuck
You you and Eric or I couldn't remember his name by the way until you said it but you and Eric you're twins, man
You you know what he's doing. He's I'm going hard
The multiple concussions you ever had a concussion to where you repeat yourself. I don't know
I don't know if I have I wake up in hospitals all the time dude, and they're like
You know where you're at and I was like, well, you're a doctor, so I'm in a hospital like what the fuck
Like I remember when Eric was in a coma and they helicoptered him off the mountain
I was like, dude, what the fuck dude? He woke up. He's fine. Let him go
Yeah, but like as a twin did you understand that he was in a coma? Did you know like did you do that when?
Connecting whatever
I had his whole nose peeled off and he thought I was him.
He's like, oh my God, you're okay.
I was like, no, no, no, I'm his twin brother.
No, no, no, that's not what I mean.
I mean, like, did you know at that moment as a twin,
like there's something wrong with my twin?
I was like, he just got a broken rib, you're fine,
dude, he was literally a little bit fucked inside.
Oh, that was it, okay.
That's like me, that's like me and my brother being like,
I'm like, dude, you'll be fine.
look I drove everybody back home dude and then we went back to the hospital
and I was like I walked in I was like how's he doing so did you bring him in I was like yeah
the doctor like had me all weird and shit and I was like what he was all he was literally like a
30 minutes dude you're like you're like me with my brother man my mom my mom calls me right and
Fuck this finger up. And yeah, it was like a skeleton. You could see the skeleton part
And I was and and yeah, yeah, and like he was like
Trying to call me
He's trying to call me dude, and I'm like
We'll get to me. I don't have a ride get to me and then I can drive your ride
and bloods everywhere and I saw his skeleton finger and I took him to the fucking hospital and
yep they fucking preserved it. So what eventually had happened was, dumbass, he slammed the garage door down on his finger and it busted it.
But I didn't know if you if you were like your brother like twins or whatever like can you feel that he's
Fuck no, dude, dude, I was going up the lift and I was like, is that him in the ski patrol dude right there with the
What's up with those twins what's up with those twins that can like do that like
Telepathic bullshit horse again brothers. It was Cheech and Chong, bro
The Corsican brothers, do you remember them?
Hey, this motherfucker was on the verge of death, dude.
And we're just making fun of him.
It's kind of sad.
We're going to the gas station getting nachos and shit.
He's like, I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
And he literally was dying.
He was going to die.
He was bleeding out, internally bleeding.
It happened to me twice, dude.
I was in the hospital for over two weeks every time.
They kept my spleen the guy's all your hemoglobin levels seems to be not going below
Give me the fuck feeling good
Dude, I got bit by a brown recluse though. That was one of my
The mark for it. I have it just right here on my neck dude and fucking I was on your neck
I got it on my thigh, dude
that just connected with my body.
First it was like a golf ball
and they gave me a shot of penicillin in my ass.
Is that, it gets worse.
Oh, you went and got medication for it?
I didn't even fucking do anything.
And then, and then so then I woke up at like four
in the morning and it was like, I couldn't breathe.
And I was all, oh, what the fuck's going on?
Oh, it fucked you up that bad?
Well, dude, I-
Shit.
I just, dude, when I got bit, bro, look,
when I got bit, it was on my thigh.
on my elder thigh and I was like fuck it felt like fire and then it was like this big blister
and then I popped the blister and it was fire again oh dude you don't feel the bite dude that's
the thing I know yeah I was I was asleep I was in bed honestly honestly though they didn't know
but that's what they were all shooting for they're like
We think it's a brown recluse. I was like well
I have been doing community service in a park didn't I've been fucking cutting bushes and breaking fucking shit all over the place
I'm pretty sure I threw some
But dude, they told me to gently nudge it and keep the whole clean
And I was like okay, and they put pen marks all over my face, and I was all fuck
No, shut up. I said I said fuck this dude
I grabbed a fist on either side of my neck, bro, and I popped it like a fire hydrant
did yeah well you guess what when you here's our problem when when you pop
it it's worse so what it did is turned into staff infection
Right, exactly where I was going with it, and fucking I popped it, but guess what I did?
I knew immediately, I was like, oh man, I got big.
You gotta get the whole sack out, bro.
No, no, no.
So what I did was, is I got antibacterial gel, and I started rubbing it, and then I would
let it breathe.
And then I would put it back on, and I would let it breathe.
Yeah, but now I have a big
Brown recluse scar on my fucking outer leg. Yeah, if you let it too long bro, dude, you're just getting amputated
Everything gets cut off. Do it. Yeah, I had a big old thing dangling out of the hole dude
And I grabbed it was like thicker and longer than a pencil, bro
I ripped the whole sack out dude, and they tripped out. What did you do with it?
I was like I flushed it down the toilet and rinsed it down the sink dude. I was like what the fuck
kept me for two weeks and oh and mind you I miss I was missing my last day of
community service and I and if you do community service and you're like I'm
gonna do 10 days in a row you miss a day you have to reinstate and do it all
over so I'm on the phone tell me yeah if you're gonna have to reinstate and I
talked to them dude they called me back and they're like
They've out of out of the 16 years they were having that program and ranch Cucamonga did the state park
They said I was the best worker they've ever had bro, and they fucking branded me my last day
So I didn't have to do it. You want to know the part about that? I saw that I saw that with you
No this motherfucker
He right when I walked up to him, dude. He's all I know and I was a what he's all I know
That's not right man. I know what you're saying
When I saw when I saw you like just working, you know doing your thing
I know that you're a drunk. You're a drunk
No, this was clear
Way before I
Hear me out
I can't say be 18 a couple months, bro. It's a little fucking shit box
I'm a fucker. I'm a fucker like six one big-ass boy
It's cool. He's a little track star. Yeah, yeah fucking run it dog
Why is it all muted do it happen?
It's sort of God bro. Did I this thing sucks. It just mutes on its own
Can't hear you dude. I just so you know I can't hear anything. It's muted for me for some reason did I get the mute button?
They're all rejoined
And those that don't remember when your shadow moved before your feet
Whispered things you couldn't keep
The walls would breathe in slow and low
Every secret you don't show
Every version left behind
Still alive inside your mind
You said
Pieces of yourself faces hanging in the air try them on if you still care
Every mask of life you wore every life still wanting more you said
Some things always watching I said yes
But so
Plastic little cuts everywhere
Jokes with the blade dressed up polite
You left a bit loud but the timing ain't right
I check my pulse, said maybe it's me
But patterns don't lie, they repeat like a beat
You drop info late then call it a sip
Nah, you're playing chess while they think it's scary
from
like disaster is a farm someone hit the relics in the laundry by the stairs
someone's acting casual while conducting psychic prayers in somewhere
in the candle smoke behind the secret door a hidden high priestess knows a little something more
she never makes an entrance she just suddenly
Shit like a sweet forbidden hymns like he dreams
You're invisible, not weak.
Just too available, too eager.
Giving to people who don't respect you.
But the world doesn't care about your heart.
It cares about your value.
And if you can't control perception,
you'll spend your life being used.
Overlooked replaced
People judge with their eyes not their hands they see results not your struggle
intention and honestly they don't care about your sacrifice about your purity about your
good heart you want respect demonstrate strength you want loyalty prove value you want people
to take you seriously show them that losing you as consequences i'm not saying be cruel
i'm saying stop expecting
Purity if you feel invisible, it's not on the valuation. It's accurate valuation
Stop trying to prove your good start proving your necessary built
Our city creates value Availability destroys it
Gold is rare That's why it matters
Air is everywhere That's why it's worthless
The same rule applies to you
You when you respond to everything immediately when you never say no you're training people to disrespect you you're teaching them your time means nothing
Creates curiosity curiosity creates desire desire creates power stop pouring yourself into people who give nothing back stop being emotionally available to everyone when you become
My presence is precious, my energy
Seven keys to power, not cruelty, strategy, not manipulation, awareness, they judge you
by
What you show, not your heart, two value is the measure of worth, not effort
Three scarves, city builds power, availability destroys it for
Competence over charisma, always five
Control your emotions before they control you, six
Walking away is your greatest leverage
This is how power actually works
Machiavelli showed us 500 years ago
Most people ignored it
Wanted to believe the world was fair
That kindness wins
That hard work is enough
But you're not most people you're here
Because you want the truth
And the truth is this
The game is already being played
The only question is
Whether you're playing or not
Being played
I'm fire, everybody gotta take Names in the air like a trial I didn't make
Burn them out, pick a side, prove you're one of us Funny how fast that support turns to
pressure and disgust I said I don't know the story, am I signing up
from claims You want instant verdicts, I don't play those
games No pay for work, then I'm asking for more
That ain't defense, that's me checking the floor
You call it silence
You're supposed to be, you were back in me
Building me like in the show
Till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You want control, dressed up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
to a pile on wave, same voices yell in different names on the stage
Everyone knows, yeah, everyone says, but nobody stops to question the thread
Proof in the DMs I didn't review, or proof you decided was already true
You want me to act on a crowd-made case, then punish me when I don't keep pace
Than a few people now, I'm afraid
Or maybe I'm done with the games you play, you push iCold and call it
Like in the show, till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my platform, not your community
You don't get to vote on what I believe
You won't control, dress up as a unity
I see the strings, I don't agree
You draw your lines and expect me to trace it
Call it standards, I call it stage
Now it's noise trying to speak over me
But this is mine, not your community
But who made you judge, jury?
And now executioner live in my chat?
Nah.
Standing where I choose to be
Yeah, this is mine
Not your community
You are not dragging, you are cargo, something else has hands on the wheel, and it knows your name.
Turn your bloodstream, signing all your thoughts
Smiling in the mirror while you're real self-wrought
It's polite, little prisoner, trained to obey
You call it being good, but you're decaying that way
You swallow every instinct, fire your teeth down smooth
Call it self-control, but you just removed your poof, your hat claws
You had fire, you had something divine
Now you apologize for crossing your own line
Call John Whisper from the grave
Make the dark conscious, or it digs your cave
But you muted the message, sanitized the pain
Now your shadow's in the-
You have a use of and I pretend it's you
Take back the throne, reclaim the room
Turn your shadow from a cage
Into a weaponized bloom
You built a mask so perfect even you forgot
Polished every angle to your soul got caught
They don't love you, they love the role you placed
And an ovation for a ghost in a display
Laugh on command
You fake is a fracturing you you feel that hollowness that echo in space that your real self
I'm pretending it's you
Take back the throne, reclaim the room
Turn your shadow from a cage
Into a weaponized gloom
Everything you hate is a mirror
Every trigger gets clearer
Arrogance, that's your buried ground
Laziness, that's burnout drown
Jealousy maps where your hunger lives
Raid shows what your silence gives
Your enemies are blueprints in disguise
them right, you weaponized.
Permission to exist as a man
The moment you stop apologizing for a breath
Is the moment your presence starts to fire
Talk to your moves like they're sitting across
Negotiate storms instead of taking the loss
That voice in your chest isn't random or faded
It's a signal
reality starts bending around you
the door is still open